<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bare Bones Cooking</title><description>Fresh. Seasonal. Delicious.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 00:32:25 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Thai Tofu Lettuce Wraps</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-ord.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11116743_358934017643903_2133455565_n.jpg" alt="TofuLettuceWraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to talk about something that maybe new and different to many of you...Tofu.  Don’t be scared. When cooked correctly, it can be an awesome meatless option.  I have been trying to make tofu delicious for quite some time now, and I have finally figured it out! I have tried many different ways: pan frying, baking, grilling, etc.   The problem is that you want all the moisture out of your tofu and you want your final product to be crispy (and saucy).  I break down my tofu preparation methods below, but after that, the possibilities are endless.  Here, I decided to try a really fun take on serving the tofu, by putting it in lettuce wraps.  These are bright, colorful, light, and absolutely delicious.  I challenge you to try making tofu this way, especially if it is your first time. I think you will love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wraps&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 block tofu - extra firm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half a red bell pepper - sliced thin, 1 inch pieces &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 carrot - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 scallions - sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful of cilantro - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chopped peanuts or cashews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crisp green lettuce leaves for the wraps - cabbage works best&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sauce&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup creamy peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup low sodium soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 &amp;amp; ½ teaspoon sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon sriracha - or more based on spice preference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 teaspoons honey - can add more depending on saltiness of soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 clove of garlic - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tofu Prep: Most tofu is packed in water, and in order to achieve a desired crispiness, you must take the time to dry it completely. I usually start my tofu prep 1-2 hours before dinner.  First, drain the block and wrap around a clean kitchen towel. Put a pan or something heavy on top and let sit for 30 minutes. Next, cut tofu into 8 equal rectangular logs and do the same - place in paper towel and let more moisture come out.  Do this for as long as you can, but at least 20-30 minutes. At this point, preheat your oven to 400. Take each log, and cut into 8 equal cubes(about 1 inch each). Bake in the oven on a lined baking sheet for 25 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/10560924_767540033354108_307437880_n.jpg" alt="Tofu Lettuce Wraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the tofu bakes, prepare your sauce. Whisk ingredients together and let the flavors mingle. Sauce may be think, you can thin it out with 1-2 teaspoons of water, and whisk again to incorporate. Once the tofu comes out of the oven, throw into the sauce and let it absorb the delicious flavors for 15-20 minutes. At this point, you can saute your pepper and carrot shreds in about a teaspoon of oil. After the tofu is marinated, toss it in the pan with the veggies. Let it get thick and crispy for about 5 minutes. It may stick, let it, thats great flavor. At the end, toss in half the scallions and the cilantro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11078749_1573529312902793_997753277_n.jpg" alt="Tofu Lettuce Wraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve : Grab the outer pieces of the lettuce and lay on a plate. Fill each lettuce cup with as much filling as desired, a drizzle of more peanut sauce, more scallion, the peanuts, and sriracha (if you like spice!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are finger lickin’ good! You definitely won’t miss the meat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/thai-tofu-lettuce-wraps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00c18c57-8b77-4b06-8780-2a26434d5341</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 02:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/10963877_855813674485260_196770776_n.jpg" alt="Sausage Broccoli Rabe Pasta"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s recipe is a special one because I created it for my husband's birthday.  This is a collaboration of two of Nate’s favorite things: stuffed shells and the Italian combination of sausage, broccoli rabe, and provolone.  Let’s face it, stuffed shells is not something you make on a regular basis, as it can be time consuming.  But let me tell you this, on a Sunday afternoon with time to spare, it can be fun! Open up a bottle of wine, slice up a baguette and you have yourself a lovely evening. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with most of my recipes, things can be swapped and adjusted to your taste. Broccoli rabe can be extremely bitter, you either hate it or love it. If you dislike it, spinach would be a great swap. Just make sure you get extra since it cooks down a great deal. We like the spicy sausage in this house, but the sweet italian sausage would make a nice stuffed shell as well. As far as sauce goes, just use your favorite and you can use as little or as much as you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this for your next birthday dinner!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb spicy Italian sausage - can substitute sweet sausage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bunch of broccoli rabe - stems removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 garlic cloves - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup part skim ricotta cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 box (1 lb) of large shells&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;freshly grated provolone cheese, just a bit for the top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;approximately 3 cups of your favorite basic marinara sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set oven to 350 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set a large pot of water to boil for the pasta. While waiting, squeeze the sausage out of the casing. If bulk sausage is available in the market, choose that, as it is easier to break up and saute. Cook sausage over medium heat and break up into smaller pieces while it is cooking. Once cooked through, remove from the pan and put into a large bowl to cool. Using the same pan, add olive oil and saute the broccoli rabe. All I did to prepare the broccoli was cut off the stems and then cut the tops a few more times so the pieces are more manageable. This will cook down similar to spinach. After about 5-7 minutes and once wilted, add salt, pepper, and the garlic. Saute for another 2-3 minutes and then remove from heat and add to the bowl with the sausage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let the mixture cool a bit, and then add both cheeses, the egg, and a pinch of salt and pepper. Mix well and that is your filling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cook pasta according to package instructions, but make sure you pull just short of finished, (al dente) since the pasta will cook more in the oven. Drain pasta. Next, it is time to stuff your shells. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11111452_372256539645628_677314842_n.jpg" alt="Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stuff about a tablespoon of filling into each shell and set side by side in a baking dish. You do not want the shells to be overfilled, but just stuffed to the brim. Once all the shells are stuffed and in the pan, grate provolone cheese over the top.  Cover the shells with as much marinara sauce as you prefer and then grate more provolone cheese on top of that.  You can never have too much cheese in an Italian meal!  Cover the shells in foil and bake for 30 minutes. After 30 minutes, remove the foil and let the shells crisp up a bit, 10 - 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serve with more marinara sauce and a crusty baguette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11098238_873307906048592_2024586387_n.jpg" alt="Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/sausage-and-broccoli-rabe-stuffed-shells/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c389cbe5-5871-4c68-8e8a-3d738872bbd1</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 01:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Egg Pizzettes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093005_1608011846103503_1756062521_n.jpg" alt="Egg Pizzettes"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can have pizza for breakfast…if there’s an egg on it! Fact. I thought this would be a really fun recipe to share. Let’s be honest, this is not an everyday breakfast, but it is perfect for a lazy sunday morning or a special occasion breakfast. That is what we have here. Nate’s birthday breakfast! Believe it or not, I just used ingredients that I had on hand. That is the beauty of this. You can use any dough, any sauce, any cheese, and any veggies you have on hand. The possibilities are endless. Above is what I used for these babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red onion, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red pepper, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fresh jalepeno, sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pizza sauce - or just canned tomato sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup ricotta cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pizza dough&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preheat your oven to 450 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saute your veggies in olive oil with a pinch of salt and pepper. They don’t have to be fully cooked, just enough to lose their crunch. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by rolling your pizza dough into small round circles. You want these to be small, individual sized.  Spread each with a thin layer of sauce and ricotta cheese. Focus on the perimeter, leaving the middle empty so there is room for an egg.  Next add veggies. Again, only around the outsides, leaving the center clear. Once ready, bake pizza for approximately 8 minutes.  Remove pizza from oven, crack an egg in the middle of each and pop back in oven for approximately another 6 minutes. You want the egg to be set, but still have a runny yolk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are such a fun take on “breakfast pizza.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11095611_1625411984344687_494048752_n.jpg" alt="Egg Pizzettes"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/egg-pizzettes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ca2ecf6d-5040-490e-83e7-da9337915723</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to BareBonesCooking everyone! I am extremely excited to start sharing my recipes with my family and friends. I will try to keep my recipes fairly simple and straight-forward, but if you ever have a question, just ask! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose this recipe to start, because it is simple, easily customizable, and takes less than 30 minutes to make. This makes it an easy weeknight meal and it is really satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used shrimp, but any protein will work, and tofu would be great as well.  The veggies can be swapped out, too. This just happens to be my favorite combo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to get cooking!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11032796_389444547908175_1430500394_n.jpg" alt="Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb shrimp - peeled and deveined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half of a white onion - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 red bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a cup of peas - fresh or frozen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can full fat coconut milk*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small jar (or 3-4 tablespoons) red curry paste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can light coconut milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup jasmine rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*can use light coconut milk, it will just make sauce thinner&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start by putting your rice on the burner so it will be finished by the time the dish is ready.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add 1 can of coconut milk and about another cup of water to the pot. Note: the liquid amount will depend on which rice you decide to use. For any white rice it is usually a 2 to 1 ratio, but a brown rice may differ, so check the package directions.  Once boiling, add in the rice and salt to taste, it definitely needs a little salt to round out the flavor.  Cover and simmer for approximately 15 minutes or as directed on package.  Turn off burner and let rice steam until curry is ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093037_1559802824294336_1848730949_n.jpg" alt="Curry"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by sauteing your onion for about 5 minutes until softened. Add in pepper and let that cook for another few minutes. Stir in the curry paste and let it infuse the veggies and soften up a bit. Stir in coconut milk and increase the heat to bring it to a simmer. At this point, you can add in your shrimp. I usually pat my shrimp dry and add salt and pepper.  Add them into the pot and let them simmer for 3-5 minutes, depending on the size of the shrimp.  At the end, throw in the thawed peas and let them bubble for a minute in the sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serve this over coconut rice!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/red-curry-shrimp-with-coconut-rice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b17f3d61-5575-4170-99c0-cf6e8b8010a4</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>