<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bare Bones Cooking</title><description>Fresh. Seasonal. Delicious.</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:45:39 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://barebonescooking.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Spinach Poppy Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-atl.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11243850_366276456900133_308885176_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to start by saying that I am sorry for posting another salad recipe this soon, but I absolutely have to share this one! Plus, it’s spring-time and I think we all can use a little more salad in our lives. This dressing is a real winner.  It is sweet, savory, and salty, with a nice bite from the onion.  The ingredients go nicely together and really compliment and balance each other. This salad makes a great lunch or side for dinner. I think it would also be lovely at a BBQ as a light and fresh option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, of course you can tweak the salad ingredients to use what you have and what you like. That is what I always do, and that is what inspired this salad! Hope you enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;spinach leaves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup cooked whole wheat pasta (optional - I used leftovers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sliced strawberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup of crumbled feta - to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful roasted sunflower seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poppy Seed Dressing &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup white vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp white sugar &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp grated white onion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp poppy seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 heaping tbsp dijon mustard &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by making the dressing. Add the sugar to the vinegar and whisk until sugar is dissolved, about 2 minutes. Next, add grated onion - I use a regular box grater on the large holes to do this. This will give you the onion flavor without the sharp bite. Add the dijon mustard and then the olive oil and whisk until emulsified. Add the poppy seeds at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the spinach and pasta to a large bowl and continue to add each layer on top. Mix with dressing and serve with extra sunflower seeds on top for a little added crunch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11252886_691378404342000_1821008213_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/spinach-poppy-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0d1023ff-0228-4151-baf5-0c2f50e248d3</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farro with Mushrooms</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11236294_832794346756139_1889030388_n.jpg" alt="Farro with Mushrroms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great little side dish! Let me start by telling you about farro. It is one of my new favorite grains! The thing that I love about it is its texture and its chewiness. In my opinion, it is more interesting than quinoa and couscous. Don’t get me wrong - I love those as well, but quinoa is lacking texture and couscous can just be boring sometimes.  That is where farro comes in - to spice things up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The definition of farro, straight from the wikipedia article is : “a food composed of the grains of certain wheat species. The exact definition is debated.” So you’ll just have to trust me and try it yourself! I find it in my local supermarket with the rice and the grains, but you can sometimes find it in the bulk bins of certain health food stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been experimenting with it lately, and it can really stand up to most “dressings” and ingredients. Here, I tried to make it a savory side to go with the salmon and asparagus we were having for dinner.  The garlic butter is fantastic and really soaks into the farro. Who doesn’t love garlic butter slathered on anything and everything?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I want to take some time to talk about the mushrooms. Mushrooms can be a finicky ingredient if not prepared properly. After some testing around, I think I have found a delicious way to bring out their flavor. Just want to give a shout-out to my friend Kelly for helping me perfect this technique. More on that below…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups farro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cups low sodium chicken stock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 package mushrooms - any kind you like&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ stick of butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cloves of garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup cooking sherry - available in the supermarket&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by bringing the chicken stock and water to boil in a medium sauce pan. I like to always use low sodium chicken stock so I can control the amount of salt in the recipe. Once boiling, add in farro and some salt. You can adjust this later if you didn't add enough. One thing about farro, is that all the liquid does not have to evaporate like it does for rice. Most of the time, you have to drain the farro at the end of cooking it. After you add the farro in, reduce the heat to a simmer and put a lid on it. It will need to cook about 30 minutes until tender but still chewy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11241894_890291644363578_507844597_n.jpg" alt="Farro with Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the farro is cooking , slice your mushrooms if they are not already sliced and heat a saute pan on medium high heat. Put the mushrooms in the pan DRY. No oil, no salt, nothing to begin with. Mushrooms have liquid in them, and when you salt them early, they get watery. Give the mushrooms a few minutes to soften, then they will release liquid for a few minutes and dry up and begin to stick to the pan. At this point, after about 10 minutes, add in the sherry and let the mushrooms cook until they are dry again. Add in salt and a good dose of fresh cracked black pepper. Set aside until farro is done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a small saucepan, heat the butter and grate in your garlic using a microplane. You could also just mince finely. Let them melt together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drain your farro, place it in a bowl, and then pour the hot garlic butter over top. Smells so good! Top the bowl with the sauted mushrooms and dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11274374_1444262582551457_1082559282_n.jpg" alt="Farro with mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/farro-with-mushrooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4b2cbaa9-d656-4a84-9dba-52f786c1085c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:59:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mango Slaw</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-iad.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11243878_724515674325519_703809639_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the slaw I served alongside the double bean burgers I posted earlier this week. It is so perfect for the grilling season and will be a great accompaniment to your BBQ’s.  It comes together in no-time and all the ingredients are fresh. I have a feeling this will be on a regular rotation through the spring and summer cook-out season. It is crunchy, tangy, and sweet from the mango. What more could you ask for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;  
  &lt;li&gt;1/4 cup greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;    
  &lt;li&gt;¼ cup mayo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;lime juice - 1/2 a lime&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp dijon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;* ½ tsp celery seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ small green cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ small red cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 ripe mango - peeled and sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red pepper - sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*I used ½ tsp of celery salt, so I omitted any extra salt. If you use plain celery seed, you may still need to add a pinch of salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, make the dressing. Combine all the ingredients, mix, and taste for seasoning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chop and slice all your veggies and mango. Add in dressing and put it in the fridge so the flavors can meld. I did not use all the dressing. I would start with half, and then adjust from there. Sometimes, after it sits a while, it soaks up dressing and you need to add more later, so save some.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11263295_1600953910175582_460942730_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is really a perfect side dish for any BBQ, burgers, grilled chicken, seafood, and everything! The best part is, it gets better the longer it sits, so it is a perfect make-ahead dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll want to save this recipe for your upcoming summer BBQ’s!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/mango-slaw/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ef8de63e-52da-4cd0-b2bb-086529d7cc5c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 00:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Double Bean Burgers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11232777_669494849850530_228232587_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burger"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband and I can both agree - my black bean burger game has come a LONG way! I have been “attempting” to make non-mushy black bean burgers for years now, and I am happy to say that I have finally mastered it! I’m sure many of you have tried to make some form of bean burgers and they have not been the consistency you were hoping for. I have tried pan frying, baking, and even grilling. I would not try grilling, trust me. However, I have had great success in the combination of freezing the burgers, baking the burgers on high heat, then broiling them, which gives you a “burger-like” consistency and can stand up on a bun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are so great because they are an awesome meat free option, very filling, and you can play around with the ingredients and toppings to make what you like. I used a mixture of black beans and cannellini beans because I think the cannellini beans are so smooth and creamy that they balance out the black beans. You can add more or less spice with the jalapenos and chili powder. The toppings I used really compliment the black bean burger nicely, but the sky's the limit! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chipotle mayo is so smoky and a bit spicy, the avocado is cool and creamy, and the sprouts are a fun and fresh twist. I do not usually use spouts in my cooking, but I love them when I eat them out. I saw them in my supermarket and scooped them right up for this recipe. I plan on using them top top sandwiches and wraps for the next week or 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make these for your next meatless Monday or for your vegetarian friend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burgers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cans black beans - rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can cannellini beans - rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large jalapeno, seeds removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cloves of garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1  cup panko bread crumbs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 1/2 tsp ground cumin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½-1 tsp chili powder (if you like spice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixins'&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hamburger buns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avocado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;greens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;red onion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chipotle mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup mayo or light mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tsp chipotles in adobo (I use the juice and not the actual peppers - can adjust to spice level)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, give the peppers, garlic, and cilantro a rough dice. Toss them into the food processor and pulse until they are diced fine. Drain and rinse the beans and add them to a large bowl. Using your hands, get in there and “smoosh” the beans up. Of course you can use a fork if you’d like, but my grandmother always said - “a cook’s best tools are her hands.” She still cooks that way today. Add the food processor mix to the beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, add the seasoning and taste. This is your chance to taste before you add the egg. Add in the egg and mix to combine the mixture.  Add panko bread crumbs and stir. These should soak up some of the excess liquid and make the mixture more dry. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11256826_504694216349926_863440241_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, I form my beans into burger patties on parchment paper or a silpat baking mat. Put the burgers into the freezer to firm up for about 1/2 hour - 1 hour.  Preheat the oven to 400 degrees.  You can take the burgers straight from the freezer to the oven.  Bake the burgers for 20 minutes on 400 degrees then put them on the broil setting for 3-5 minutes to crisp up the tops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the mayo, just mix the 2 together and save for the topping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11251145_842855302453170_841597462_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve, add your burger to the bun, top with chipotle mayo, red onion, avocado, and alfalfa sprouts. I served mine alongside my mango slaw, which I will post later this week. Stay tuned...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11236410_626942004108157_1412163059_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/double-bean-burgers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03b07877-7d67-49d5-b4c1-ad29291b1096</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Pil-Pil</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11192926_1390312407962346_2082094703_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Pil-Pil"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is my take on one of my favorite appetizers, served at a quaint little Greek restaurant that we used to live by. Since we lived across the street, we frequented &lt;a href="http://www.dmitrisrestaurant.com/2nd.html"&gt;Dimitris&lt;/a&gt; numerous times, and always ended up with this appetizer since we loved it so much.  What we know : it’s spicy, it’s garlicky, and it is crispy and delicious. I think I came pretty close to recreating this recipe on the first try.  Before writing this, I did a quick google search and learned that this a common tapas recipe from Spain, called Gambas al Ajillo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since returning from our trip to the islands of Belize, I have been craving seafood. On the islands, it is so easy because it is always the fresh catch of the day. I ate fish and seafood every night and loved it. I have been inspired to try more fish dishes and experiment with new types of fish and seafood. I hope to have some new and exciting fish dishes coming up in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 serrano chile, diced fine (can sub jalapeno)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ lb of shrimp - peeled and deveined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 cloves of garlic, minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 scallion, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ teaspoon red pepper flakes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cilantro - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ ¼ cup flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;squeeze of lemon, optional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin, make sure shrimp are cleaned and patted until completely dry. Add salt and pepper to shrimp and then dunk them in the flour, covering all sides with a light coat. Next prepare your veg. Dice the chile, garlic, and scallion.  Add oil to the pan and let it sizzle. Add in just the chile and scallion and let it cook for about 3 minutes. Add your dredged shrimp and let it cook and crisp up. It can take about 3-5 minutes per side, depending on the size of your shrimp. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11184474_2030452110427040_1049964850_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Pil-Pil"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you flip the shrimp, add the garlic in. Garlic has a tendency to burn, so we want to prevent this by adding it later. Once the shrimp is almost done, toss everything together in the pan. Add in chili flakes and cilantro and let the flavors marry. Make sure you scrape up all the bits of flavor from the bottom of the pan. Serve with a squeeze of lemon, and even grilled bread to sop up the excess!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/shrimp-pil-pil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">cb68552e-3f46-4725-b47a-b16eb4158bd2</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 01:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicken Ka-pita-bobs</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11190989_850501015016073_1897984115_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you are thinking - Is it a kabob or a pita? Well I thought it would be fun to turn the chicken kabobs into a Greek/Lebanese style pita with tzatziki! It spices up your chicken routine and you can make it on the grill. I want to say grilling season is here for good, but who knows with this weather! Hopefully it will turn around in May. Once we start grilling outside, we grill straight through until winter hits. It is so nice to be outside grilling, plus it is less dishes!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is just a basic and easy marinade. As for the veggies, you can use what you like, I just used onions this time. The tzatziki recipe is actually not my own. I know I am Lebanese and I am positive my gram has a spectacular recipe for this, but I have been making Ina Garten’s recipe for years, and it is just too good to change. It is utterly perfect and we love it every time. I will post a link to it so you can check it out. You can top these pitas with tomatoes, onions, pickles, anything you like. They are healthy and delicious way to jump out of that grilled chicken rut!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kabobs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 pounds of chicken breasts or tenders, cut into 1 inch cubes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lemon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 garlic cloves, minced or grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons fresh dill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large white onion, cut into chunks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;skewers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pitas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pitas, I used whole wheat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fixins : tomatoes, red onions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/ina-garten/easy-tzatziki-with-toasted-pita-crisps-recipe.html"&gt;Tzatziki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that if I take the extra time out to marinate the chicken, it comes out juicier in the end.  Chop the chicken into equal size cubes and place in a large ziplock bag or in a dish to marinate. Add in a good amount of salt and pepper, then the oil, lemon juice, garlic, and dill.  Marinate for at least 3 hours but up to an entire day. Once chicken is marinated, grab your skewers and thread the chicken and the white onion (or veggies), alternating. Grill the skewers until the chicken is cooked through to 165 degrees. Let them rest while you prepare the pitas, tzatziki and toppings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11203505_350166058514532_1557411626_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the pita, add a skewer of chicken meat and onions, top with tzatziki and veggies! This recipe can really be adapted to the veggies and toppings you want, so have fun with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11193173_1079468495402124_2135805408_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/chicken-ka-pita-bobs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">484575d0-3eee-430d-b706-f31a59139fda</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 00:25:22 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Light &amp; Bright Lemon Vinaigrette</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093139_1385807455080439_1009811087_n.jpg" alt="Light and Bright Lemon Vinaigrette"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey Everyone! I am back from my vacation hiatus and ready to post some light and healthy recipes. I think as soon as spring hits, we all have this mind-set to eat better, grill more, and lighten our food choices. Ironically, today is the first really nice day that feels like spring. The weather has been a real bummer lately, so what better way to “think spring” than a yummy and healthy salad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This vibrant dressing is a great all around dressing to use for salads. The lemon is bright, the garlic adds a nice bite, and the honey sweetens the whole thing up. It is a really nice, flavorful balance. I used mine on spinach greens with tomatoes and scallions, but you can use yours on any combo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup lemon juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil (I used a little less than this)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 clove of garlic, grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon of honey, can use more if you want it sweeter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a pinch of salt and pepper, to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is such a simple vinaigrette to whip up and it is great on any salad. Just whisk all the ingredients in a small bowl and dress greens. As for the actual salad, use whats fresh, use what you’ve got, and mix up what you like!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11186943_850868921627739_1823840895_n.jpg" alt="Light and Bright Lemon Vinaigtrette"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Do you see that grilled bread up there? I brushed my baguette slices with the dressing and grilled it. It tastes like a tangy garlic bread. It really is the perfect compliment to the salad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This could also be used as a marinade for chicken, fresh fish, and shrimp!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/light-bright-lemon-vinaigrette/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c363cd44-5f0a-41b2-bd69-5d612d2c986b</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 28 Apr 2015 02:32:53 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Cauliflower Mashers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11137941_1629999970578754_475505817_n.jpg" alt="Cauliflower Mashers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As promised, here is the other side dish to accompany the Easter ham. I know this has been a popular idea for some time now, but I think the roasted garlic in here really brings up the flavor.  Lets face it, cauliflower can be boring. However, cauliflower can also be transformed to mimic other things with great results. Here, you can have the creamy and satisfying texture of mashed potatoes, but it is better for you! Don’t get me wrong - this still has a fair amount of butter, but this recipe makes enough for at least 6. So all in all, it is a better way to enjoy your favorite comfort food and get a little added health benefit. Win-Win.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 heads of cauliflower&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 tablespoons of butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup buttermilk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 head of roasted garlic (recipe below)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Roasted Garlic&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Roasting garlic is a great way to add that delicious garlic flavor, without the serious bite.  The roasting process mellows and sweetens the flavor of the garlic. It definitely has its place in cooking, and I think it fits perfectly in mashed potatoes and the like. You start with an entire clove (or 2) of garlic and you slice off the pointed tip, exposing just a tiny bit of each clove. Leave the root end intact. Flip garlic with the root end down and place on a piece of foil. Drizzle with olive oil and a pinch of salt and pepper and cover tightly. Place in the oven on 375 degrees for 50-60 minutes until fragrant and soft. Your house will smell amazing! Once finished, allow to cool.  In order to get the cloves out, squeeze close to the root end and the cloves will just pop right out.  You can even make this ahead or make multiple and keep in the fridge for other uses.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;u&gt;Cauliflower&lt;/u&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by cutting cauliflower off of the stem into smaller pieces.  Set a large pot of water on the stove and bring to a boil. Boil the cauliflower until soft, the softer it is, the easier to mash. It took me about 15 minutes to boil. To mash the cauliflower, you can use an immersion blender or a food processor. If you do not have either of these kitchen gadgets, you can boil longer than 15 minutes and use a potato masher, but they will not be as smooth.  Add in roasted garlic, butter, and buttermilk and mash together until desired creaminess. Add in a good amount of salt and fresh cracked black pepper.  This is another extremely easy side dish and a really great way to “healthify” your meal. So go ahead, go for seconds!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11137977_415671035273211_980624437_n.jpg" alt="Cauliflower Mashers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/cauliflower-mashers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">808e5016-52f8-4b22-844a-11a5b8a70ecc</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 08 Apr 2015 00:10:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Jazzed Up Peas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xap1/t51.2885-15/925581_1108381415845655_899603304_n.jpg" alt="Jazzed Up Peas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I claimed a free ham from my grocery store for the holidays, we decided to have an impromptu Easter dinner.  Unfortunately, I had to work Easter day.  Lucky for me, my husband was in charge of the shopping, the ham, and all the prep! A 12 lb ham can be a bit much for just 2 people (can you say leftovers?), so we decided to invite the family over to join.  I have had 2 recipe ideas for great sides to go with the ham bouncing around in my head for a week or so.  I have always loved the classic combination of ham with peas and mashed potatoes. I decided to spruce up the peas and swap out the potatoes, and the results were fantastic!  Stay tuned for the “mashed potato” swap...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bag frozen peas (can use fresh when in season)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 slices bacon - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half of an onion - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;approximately 3-4 teaspoons of heavy cream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful of parmesan cheese (⅓ cup)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by boiling the peas for about 5-7 minutes, then drain and rinse under cold water to stop the cooking process.  Set aside and leave draining to remove most of the water. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Heat a cast iron or heavy bottomed skillet and add bacon once hot.  Use a wooden spoon to break apart pieces and cook until crispy. Once crispy, remove bacon from pan and leave all the bacon grease. Throw in onions and saute for 5-7 minutes, until softened.  Add in the peas and saute together for a few minutes, but not too long. You want the peas to stay crisp and not mushy. When I made these, I swirled 4 turns around the pan with the cream.  Then add cheese and let the flavors meld. Add a little salt and pepper to taste at the end, but keep in mind the bacon and cheese are salty.  That is it! This is a simple and really delicious way to jazz up your peas and is really nice along side a nice holiday ham. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11116780_966896166653976_1323583196_n.jpg" alt="Jazzed Up Peas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/jazzed-up-peas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">f91e7923-a53a-43ec-9af7-c61f337dfeca</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 00:40:06 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Thai Tofu Lettuce Wraps</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-ord.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11116743_358934017643903_2133455565_n.jpg" alt="TofuLettuceWraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today I want to talk about something that maybe new and different to many of you...Tofu.  Don’t be scared. When cooked correctly, it can be an awesome meatless option.  I have been trying to make tofu delicious for quite some time now, and I have finally figured it out! I have tried many different ways: pan frying, baking, grilling, etc.   The problem is that you want all the moisture out of your tofu and you want your final product to be crispy (and saucy).  I break down my tofu preparation methods below, but after that, the possibilities are endless.  Here, I decided to try a really fun take on serving the tofu, by putting it in lettuce wraps.  These are bright, colorful, light, and absolutely delicious.  I challenge you to try making tofu this way, especially if it is your first time. I think you will love it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Wraps&lt;/em&gt; &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 block tofu - extra firm&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half a red bell pepper - sliced thin, 1 inch pieces &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 carrot - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 scallions - sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful of cilantro - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chopped peanuts or cashews&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Crisp green lettuce leaves for the wraps - cabbage works best&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Sauce&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup creamy peanut butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup low sodium soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 &amp;amp; ½ teaspoon sesame oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon sriracha - or more based on spice preference&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 teaspoons honey - can add more depending on saltiness of soy sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 clove of garlic - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Tofu Prep: Most tofu is packed in water, and in order to achieve a desired crispiness, you must take the time to dry it completely. I usually start my tofu prep 1-2 hours before dinner.  First, drain the block and wrap around a clean kitchen towel. Put a pan or something heavy on top and let sit for 30 minutes. Next, cut tofu into 8 equal rectangular logs and do the same - place in paper towel and let more moisture come out.  Do this for as long as you can, but at least 20-30 minutes. At this point, preheat your oven to 400. Take each log, and cut into 8 equal cubes(about 1 inch each). Bake in the oven on a lined baking sheet for 25 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/10560924_767540033354108_307437880_n.jpg" alt="Tofu Lettuce Wraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the tofu bakes, prepare your sauce. Whisk ingredients together and let the flavors mingle. Sauce may be think, you can thin it out with 1-2 teaspoons of water, and whisk again to incorporate. Once the tofu comes out of the oven, throw into the sauce and let it absorb the delicious flavors for 15-20 minutes. At this point, you can saute your pepper and carrot shreds in about a teaspoon of oil. After the tofu is marinated, toss it in the pan with the veggies. Let it get thick and crispy for about 5 minutes. It may stick, let it, thats great flavor. At the end, toss in half the scallions and the cilantro.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11078749_1573529312902793_997753277_n.jpg" alt="Tofu Lettuce Wraps"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve : Grab the outer pieces of the lettuce and lay on a plate. Fill each lettuce cup with as much filling as desired, a drizzle of more peanut sauce, more scallion, the peanuts, and sriracha (if you like spice!).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are finger lickin’ good! You definitely won’t miss the meat.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/thai-tofu-lettuce-wraps/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">00c18c57-8b77-4b06-8780-2a26434d5341</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 02:10:20 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/10963877_855813674485260_196770776_n.jpg" alt="Sausage Broccoli Rabe Pasta"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Today’s recipe is a special one because I created it for my husband's birthday.  This is a collaboration of two of Nate’s favorite things: stuffed shells and the Italian combination of sausage, broccoli rabe, and provolone.  Let’s face it, stuffed shells is not something you make on a regular basis, as it can be time consuming.  But let me tell you this, on a Sunday afternoon with time to spare, it can be fun! Open up a bottle of wine, slice up a baguette and you have yourself a lovely evening. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As with most of my recipes, things can be swapped and adjusted to your taste. Broccoli rabe can be extremely bitter, you either hate it or love it. If you dislike it, spinach would be a great swap. Just make sure you get extra since it cooks down a great deal. We like the spicy sausage in this house, but the sweet italian sausage would make a nice stuffed shell as well. As far as sauce goes, just use your favorite and you can use as little or as much as you want.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Consider this for your next birthday dinner!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb spicy Italian sausage - can substitute sweet sausage&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bunch of broccoli rabe - stems removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 garlic cloves - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup part skim ricotta cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 box (1 lb) of large shells&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;freshly grated provolone cheese, just a bit for the top&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;approximately 3 cups of your favorite basic marinara sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set oven to 350 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set a large pot of water to boil for the pasta. While waiting, squeeze the sausage out of the casing. If bulk sausage is available in the market, choose that, as it is easier to break up and saute. Cook sausage over medium heat and break up into smaller pieces while it is cooking. Once cooked through, remove from the pan and put into a large bowl to cool. Using the same pan, add olive oil and saute the broccoli rabe. All I did to prepare the broccoli was cut off the stems and then cut the tops a few more times so the pieces are more manageable. This will cook down similar to spinach. After about 5-7 minutes and once wilted, add salt, pepper, and the garlic. Saute for another 2-3 minutes and then remove from heat and add to the bowl with the sausage.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let the mixture cool a bit, and then add both cheeses, the egg, and a pinch of salt and pepper. Mix well and that is your filling!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cook pasta according to package instructions, but make sure you pull just short of finished, (al dente) since the pasta will cook more in the oven. Drain pasta. Next, it is time to stuff your shells. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11111452_372256539645628_677314842_n.jpg" alt="Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stuff about a tablespoon of filling into each shell and set side by side in a baking dish. You do not want the shells to be overfilled, but just stuffed to the brim. Once all the shells are stuffed and in the pan, grate provolone cheese over the top.  Cover the shells with as much marinara sauce as you prefer and then grate more provolone cheese on top of that.  You can never have too much cheese in an Italian meal!  Cover the shells in foil and bake for 30 minutes. After 30 minutes, remove the foil and let the shells crisp up a bit, 10 - 15 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serve with more marinara sauce and a crusty baguette.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11098238_873307906048592_2024586387_n.jpg" alt="Sausage and Broccoli Rabe Stuffed Shells"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/sausage-and-broccoli-rabe-stuffed-shells/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">c389cbe5-5871-4c68-8e8a-3d738872bbd1</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 30 Mar 2015 01:43:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Egg Pizzettes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093005_1608011846103503_1756062521_n.jpg" alt="Egg Pizzettes"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can have pizza for breakfast…if there’s an egg on it! Fact. I thought this would be a really fun recipe to share. Let’s be honest, this is not an everyday breakfast, but it is perfect for a lazy sunday morning or a special occasion breakfast. That is what we have here. Nate’s birthday breakfast! Believe it or not, I just used ingredients that I had on hand. That is the beauty of this. You can use any dough, any sauce, any cheese, and any veggies you have on hand. The possibilities are endless. Above is what I used for these babies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red onion, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red pepper, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fresh jalepeno, sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pizza sauce - or just canned tomato sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup ricotta cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pizza dough&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preheat your oven to 450 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Saute your veggies in olive oil with a pinch of salt and pepper. They don’t have to be fully cooked, just enough to lose their crunch. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by rolling your pizza dough into small round circles. You want these to be small, individual sized.  Spread each with a thin layer of sauce and ricotta cheese. Focus on the perimeter, leaving the middle empty so there is room for an egg.  Next add veggies. Again, only around the outsides, leaving the center clear. Once ready, bake pizza for approximately 8 minutes.  Remove pizza from oven, crack an egg in the middle of each and pop back in oven for approximately another 6 minutes. You want the egg to be set, but still have a runny yolk.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are such a fun take on “breakfast pizza.”&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11095611_1625411984344687_494048752_n.jpg" alt="Egg Pizzettes"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/egg-pizzettes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ca2ecf6d-5040-490e-83e7-da9337915723</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:52:25 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to BareBonesCooking everyone! I am extremely excited to start sharing my recipes with my family and friends. I will try to keep my recipes fairly simple and straight-forward, but if you ever have a question, just ask! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose this recipe to start, because it is simple, easily customizable, and takes less than 30 minutes to make. This makes it an easy weeknight meal and it is really satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used shrimp, but any protein will work, and tofu would be great as well.  The veggies can be swapped out, too. This just happens to be my favorite combo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to get cooking!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11032796_389444547908175_1430500394_n.jpg" alt="Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb shrimp - peeled and deveined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half of a white onion - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 red bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a cup of peas - fresh or frozen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can full fat coconut milk*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small jar (or 3-4 tablespoons) red curry paste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can light coconut milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup jasmine rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*can use light coconut milk, it will just make sauce thinner&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start by putting your rice on the burner so it will be finished by the time the dish is ready.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add 1 can of coconut milk and about another cup of water to the pot. Note: the liquid amount will depend on which rice you decide to use. For any white rice it is usually a 2 to 1 ratio, but a brown rice may differ, so check the package directions.  Once boiling, add in the rice and salt to taste, it definitely needs a little salt to round out the flavor.  Cover and simmer for approximately 15 minutes or as directed on package.  Turn off burner and let rice steam until curry is ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093037_1559802824294336_1848730949_n.jpg" alt="Curry"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by sauteing your onion for about 5 minutes until softened. Add in pepper and let that cook for another few minutes. Stir in the curry paste and let it infuse the veggies and soften up a bit. Stir in coconut milk and increase the heat to bring it to a simmer. At this point, you can add in your shrimp. I usually pat my shrimp dry and add salt and pepper.  Add them into the pot and let them simmer for 3-5 minutes, depending on the size of the shrimp.  At the end, throw in the thawed peas and let them bubble for a minute in the sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serve this over coconut rice!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/red-curry-shrimp-with-coconut-rice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b17f3d61-5575-4170-99c0-cf6e8b8010a4</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
