<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bare Bones Cooking</title><description>Fresh. Seasonal. Delicious.</description><link>http://localhost:2368/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:37:53 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:2368/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice</title><description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to BareBonesCooking everyone! I am extremely excited to start sharing my recipes with my family and friends. I will try to keep my recipes fairly simple and straight-forward, but if you ever have a question, just ask! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I chose this recipe to start, because it is simple, easily customizable, and takes less than 30 minutes to make. This makes it an easy weeknight meal and it is really satisfying.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I used shrimp, but any protein will work, and tofu would be great as well.  The veggies can be swapped out, too. This just happens to be my favorite combo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Time to get cooking!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11032796_389444547908175_1430500394_n.jpg" alt="Red Curry Shrimp with Coconut Rice"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Curry&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb shrimp - peeled and deveined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;half of a white onion - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 red bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a cup of peas - fresh or frozen&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can full fat coconut milk*&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 small jar (or 3-4 tablespoons) red curry paste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Rice&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can light coconut milk&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup jasmine rice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;*can use light coconut milk, it will just make sauce thinner&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can start by putting your rice on the burner so it will be finished by the time the dish is ready.  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add 1 can of coconut milk and about another cup of water to the pot. Note: the liquid amount will depend on which rice you decide to use. For any white rice it is usually a 2 to 1 ratio, but a brown rice may differ, so check the package directions.  Once boiling, add in the rice and salt to taste, it definitely needs a little salt to round out the flavor.  Cover and simmer for approximately 15 minutes or as directed on package.  Turn off burner and let rice steam until curry is ready.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11093037_1559802824294336_1848730949_n.jpg" alt="Curry"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by sauteing your onion for about 5 minutes until softened. Add in pepper and let that cook for another few minutes. Stir in the curry paste and let it infuse the veggies and soften up a bit. Stir in coconut milk and increase the heat to bring it to a simmer. At this point, you can add in your shrimp. I usually pat my shrimp dry and add salt and pepper.  Add them into the pot and let them simmer for 3-5 minutes, depending on the size of the shrimp.  At the end, throw in the thawed peas and let them bubble for a minute in the sauce.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Serve this over coconut rice!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://localhost:2368/red-curry-shrimp-with-coconut-rice/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b17f3d61-5575-4170-99c0-cf6e8b8010a4</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sat, 28 Mar 2015 15:13:21 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>