<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bare Bones Cooking</title><description>Fresh. Seasonal. Delicious.</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 20:00:01 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://barebonescooking.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Greek Panzanella Chicken</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfp1/t51.2885-15/10005682_1470147496633847_148176965_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it is : the perfect summer meal! I know I have been saying this a lot, but this truly is it. It is fresh, light, healthy, and absolutely delicious. It comes together in no time and some can be made ahead of time. We are now into the perfect time of year where the tomatoes are bursting with flavor and they really shine here. The feta cheese is salty and goes perfectly with the greek salad dressing. The bread cubes are the best part; they are crunchy and they soak in all the great juices. We devoured this for dinner, each bite better as the salad sits and gains flavor. The salad portion of this meal is so good that you could even serve it as a dinner on its own!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cucumber - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large tomato - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 red onion - sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup kalamata olives - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 block feta cheese - rough chop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;baguette bread cubes - toasted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chicken thighs or chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greek Dressing (adapted from Ina Garten’s recipe on foodnetwork)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cloves garlic, grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoon dried oregano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon Dijon mustard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup red wine vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoon salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note: the dressing recipe is doubled as I listed it. If you are making the salad alone, cut it in half. I used half of the dressing for the chicken and half for the salad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make the dressing first. You will mix together the ingredients, then separate it equally in half. It makes a little less than 2 cups, so about  ¾ cups each. Use half to marinate the chicken. I marinated mine for a few hours, but the longer the better with chicken. Set the other dressing aside for later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prep all of your veggies : cucumber, tomato, red onion, olives, and feta. Add them to a large bowl and pour some of the dressing over them to begin marinating. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11424917_529247130564671_1601084377_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add your chicken to the grill or skillet and cook until finished.  While chicken is cooking, cut your baguette into large cubes. Add a thin layer of olive oil to a pan and crisp up the bread slices. They will only take 3-4 minutes per side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11356358_1088011741228190_2034377552_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella CHicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pull your chicken off the heat and let it rest. Add the bread cubes to the salad and toss the remaining dressing over the bread and mix.  To serve : put the chicken on the bottom of the plate and pile it high with the salad! This is the true taste of summer :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/t51.2885-15/10731680_1612132175717606_1091750465_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had the salad leftover the next day; the only thing you have to do is make new bread cubes because they will get soggy. The rest of the salad is even better the next day!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/greek-panzanella-chicken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">968bc3b3-bc22-4e3d-bf29-d3a009476565</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 19:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBQ Burgers with Arugula and Crispy Shallots</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xpa1/t51.2885-15/11202919_499437283548103_217523149_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These burgers are a great treat! Sometimes it is so nice and comforting to make your own fancy burgers at home on the grill.  You can cook them how you like them and the topping possibilities are endless. I just made these beauties for Sunday night dinner after a weekend of working. It was the perfect cap to end the weekend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to do something a little different and play with some topping ideas and flavor combos. These flavors compliment each other perfectly for a truly amazing burger. There are 2 types of burger making styles. The type where you add ingredients into the meat mixture and keep the toppings basic. Or the type where you keep the burger meat plain and make the toppings count. My husband and I are more into making the latter version. We keep our burger meat simple with a good dose of salt and fresh cracked black pepper and we let the toppings shine through. You can taste the delicious, juicy meat and the toppings really help to round out the flavor of each bite. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These burgers are first topped with gruyere cheese which is arguably one of the most delicious melty cheeses and perfect as a burger topper. I took shallots and sliced them thin, threw them in some flour, and shallow fried them in vegetable oil for a great salty crunch. The sauce is genius - equal parts of mayo and BBQ sauce for a creamy and tangy bite. The arugula is peppery and helps to offset the sweet BBQ sauce. Together, this makes for the perfect burger bite!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you will make these before summer ends, I promise they will not disappoint! The nice thing is that you can adapt this recipe to feed just 2 people or a whole party of people easily.  They come together quick and will definitely be memorable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb ground meat (for 4 - or you can adjust for more or less)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;burger buns of your choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gruyere cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup of arugula&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 shallots, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup flour - for dredging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 1 cup vegetable oil for shallow frying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup favorite BBQ sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by prepping your ingredients. The shallots will take the most time and prep. Heat the vegetable oil on medium heat on the stove until just before boiling.  Peel the shallots and slice them into thin rounds. Add them into the flour and lightly coat them. Once the oil is ready, drop some into the oil, but do not crowd the pan. I did these in about 3 batches. Shallow fry the shallots until brown and crispy. Once finished, add them to a paper-towel lined plate to catch the drippings. Salt them immediately after removing from the oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11352065_432081840308354_1696740413_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set the shallots aside. Get the arugula ready by washing and drying the leaves and set them aside as while. For the sauce, mix together BBQ sauce and mayo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xpa1/t51.2885-15/10809512_114169242258059_1936482464_n.jpg" alt="BBQ burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the burgers, add salt and pepper to the meat and mix with your hands quickly. Form the burgers into patties based on the size you would like. Cook the burgers on medium heat on your grill until desired doneness. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I snagged this neat little chart from food network to give you their recommended cooking temperatures. You can always cut into it to check if you don’t have a thermometer, but I highly recommend using a meat thermometer for perfect cooking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beef : Food Network Recommendation &lt;br&gt;
Rare = 125 + 3 minute rest &lt;br&gt;
Medium Rare = 130-135 &lt;br&gt;
Medium = 135-140 &lt;br&gt;
Medium Well = 140-150 &lt;br&gt;
Well = 155 + &lt;br&gt;
Ground = 160&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When burgers are almost done, add cheese so it melts. Toast buns on grill, if desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assemble burgers : Add meat/cheese to the bun, then add arugula, then shallots, and the BBQ mayo on the top. Dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11425273_761502367308824_924565761_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/bbq-burgers-with-arugula-and-crispy-shallots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8b799846-6953-4021-a18a-9109fc76191c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 21:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11333344_1581127745481976_72603921_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the summer months, we all have so many occasions that could use a great side dish like this pasta salad. There are holidays like the 4th of July that just passed, BBQ’s, potlucks, and picnics. This is such a fun spin on pasta salad and it has a lighter feel. I usually use whole wheat pasta, which helps. I gave this salad a greek spin and used kalamata olives and feta cheese because they are salty and they compliment the sweet sun-dried tomato perfectly! The arugula has a nice sharp bite and also offsets any sweetness. All of these flavors go together so nicely and are truly the perfect compliment to any meal. It goes well with meat, fish, or can even be served alone as a light lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 oz sun-dried tomatoes ~ 10 pieces packed in oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup of the oil from the sun-dried tomato jar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup arugula &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup kalamata olives - pitted and chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup feta crumbles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb pasta - I used whole wheat bowties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can begin by cooking your pasta in a large pot of salted water. Cook to al dente and drain the pasta and let it cool just a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the “sauce”, begin by pulsing the sun-dried tomatoes in the food processor. I usually dump in about ¼ cup of the oil from the sun-dried tomato jar to thin it out a bit.  Next, add an additional ½ cup of regular olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11410370_127598627574059_1152604730_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once pasta has cooled, but is still a little warm, add the parmesan cheese and mix. Then add the sun-dried sauce you made. Allow this mixture to cool in the fridge until closer to the time you are ready to serve. This pasta salad is served cold or at room temperature. After the pasta salad has cooled, add in the arugula, feta crumbles, and kalamata olives. Mix and serve immediately or chill longer to let the flavors marry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This salad is so perfect for BBQ’s or picnics because it can sit out and be served at any temperature. This recipe is a must before the end of the summer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11335538_1459471921019984_1756114588_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/sun-dried-tomato-pasta-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63cd5d33-850e-4ece-8ed4-89c57d28ee45</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 01:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Quesadillas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380960_1582324645364771_2087409641_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My apologies for posting another shrimp recipe so soon, but it is just such a great summer option! It is an easily-attainable, pretty affordable seafood option. It is nice to switch up classics with new flavors. That is just what I did here. Most people think of chicken, beef, or pork in their quesadillas, but swapping out meat for seafood is a great alternative. The shrimp is bold and spicy, the corn is sweet and fresh, and the scallions and beans are great additions. When pressed together with gooey cheddar cheese, each bite is bursting with great flavors! These are fun to serve cut up as an appetizer with a side of sour cream and tomatoes. You can also have them as a main meal with a vegetable or rice side, which is what we did. This is a great summer meal!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quesadillas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 lb peeled and deveined shrimp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flour tortillas - 2 per quesadilla (this made 5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chipotle in adobo, just the sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 corn cob - kernels removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ can black beans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 scallion - sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cheddar cheese - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toppings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pico : diced tomato, diced red onion, diced jalapeno, cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sour cream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started this off by marinating my shrimp for about half an hour while I was preparing other things. I dried off my shrimp, added salt and pepper, and brushed them with chipotle sauce. I elf the actual peppers in the can and just used the sauce. That gives plenty of spice! They do not need long to marinate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11357442_952477491483883_19807296_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the filling for the quesadillas, start by cooking the shrimp. I made them on my indoor grill. You can grill them or pan fry them, whatever is easiest. If they are small like mine were, they only need a few minutes in each side. Once cooked, add them to a medium sized bowl. To that bowl, add you cooked corn kernels, black beans and scallions. This will be you filling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380797_1602504120028225_1804088040_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a panini or sandwich press, you can use this to press the quesadillas. If not, you can press them in a pan with a heavy pan on top. Add a tortilla to the bottom, add the filling leaving a small border around the edges and pile the cheese on top. Place another tortilla on top then close the lid and let it cook until the cheese is melted. Flip the tortilla carefully and let the other side cook until finished! You can serve these in a whole circle with a big dollop of sour cream and pico or you can cut them into wedges and top each wedge with the goodies. Delicious any which way you slice it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11423000_458400464321694_537719983_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/srimp-quesadillas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b76b5630-e963-49a9-94c7-df2ed039a9ca</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 01:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poppin' Cherry Chicken</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11355866_410440285806013_615903290_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here we have a perfect summer meal. Summertime is the best time for tomatoes to shine. This recipe is my spin on the classic chicken parm. The chicken is crispy and flavorful. The spinach is healthy and garlicky. The tomatoes are sweet and burst with flavor in your mouth. The cheese on top is ooey and gooey and ties everything together. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had this for Sunday dinner for my brother and his girlfriend. It was pretty fun to have extra hands in the kitchen to help with the prep. So bring your family, friends, and kids into the kitchen and make this before summer is over!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups bread crumbs ( I used seasoned)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*6 thin sliced chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint cherry tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 oz fresh mozzarella&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bag spinach &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cloves of garlic - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*the chicken must be sliced thin - if you buy the large chicken breasts, cut them in half lengthwise &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this meal, I find it best to prep all of the parts and then assemble the chicken and bake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the chicken breading : &lt;br&gt;
Begin by setting up your breading station. Add the flour, eggs, and breadcrumbs each into a separate container. Pat your chicken dry and add salt and pepper. Next, dip the chicken in flour, then into the egg, and finally into the breadcrumbs. Set on a late until you are ready to pan-fry. Once you are ready to cook, shallow fry each piece in enough olive oil to coat the pan. Since they are thin, they will cook quickly - 3-4 minutes per side. Once cooked, add to a paper towel to drain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cherry Tomatoes : &lt;br&gt;
Add oil, salt, and pepper to tomatoes and roast on 350 degrees for 20 minutes. You want the tomatoes to be at the point where they just burst (see below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11326823_457678617737930_203090873_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spinach : &lt;br&gt;
Saute in olive oil to wilt the spinach down. After about 5-7 minutes when it is cooked, add a pinch of salt and pepper and the minced garlic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11410616_1598583070403518_491274640_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Dish : &lt;br&gt;
Take a piece of chicken and add the spinach on top. Next, add the cherry tomatoes and mozzarella cheese.  Since everything is already cooked at this point, we just want to melt the cheese. Put your oven on the broil setting and broil the chicken on the top rack for 2-3 minutes until cheese is melted and bubbly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11376712_826271174128146_223030176_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I served this alongside a simple pasta with the rest of the roasted tomatoes from the prep, roasted garlic, and parmesan cheese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11356000_828117400611018_1885508556_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/poppin-cherry-chicken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">97cd1e9f-9de5-45cf-8f45-b8159320ed46</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 01:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Corn Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11421971_386701731520252_1465121388_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This type of salad seems to be a staple in my family for most summer BBQ’s. Since summer corn has such a small window, we make the most of it as long as we can. When we enjoy corn on the cob, we usually leave the husk on the corn and grill it just like that. For this, I thought I would switch it up and boil the corn then use my indoor grill since the weather was bad. This makes it an easy option if you are already in the kitchen cooking. However, if you are already grilling, throw those babies on the grill and you’ll have the same outcome. The salad is light and refreshing for the summer weather and pairs nicely with most meat and seafood dishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11420907_1459180354375471_1371722305_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint cherry tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 ears corn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 oz small mozzarella balls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 scallions- sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 tbsp honey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;juice of 3-4 limes ~ 1/3 cup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by slicing the mozzarella balls in half. If the cherry tomatoes are large, you can slice these in half too. Slice the scallions and set all of these in a large bowl.  For the corn, you can grill it or boil it. I did both! A boil to cook it and a quick flip on the grill for color and some char. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11380172_952825744775770_1228231415_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a great trick for you to get the kernels off that cobb in the easiest and cleanest way possible.  See my picture below : place a small bowl upside down in a large bowl, then place the corn cobb on the base of the small bowl and stead it. Using a sharp knife, shave the kernels off from top to bottom, so that they fall nicely in the bowl. So easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11357682_334399986684030_1201146520_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the dressing, it is based on your preference. It is just lime juice with honey, and salt and pepper. You can add more honey for sweetness or more lime for more tartness. Also, if you are making this ahead, you may want to make extra dressing since it will soak into the veggies. This is such a delicious, colorful side dish for any barbeque, picnic, or dinner this summer!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/summer-corn-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6f842036-42c9-4683-a19a-7350825b16ec</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 19:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Cheesecake Bars</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380738_935501613178740_1446684649_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend we celebrated my Dad’s birthday. His one request was that we have a BBQ at his house and everyone makes something. My brother had a menu in mind, so we all split up the dishes evenly. My dad made the steak and lobster, my mom made the chimichurri sauce and sides, my brother made a summer grilled corn salad, Nate made fresh baked bread and trout dip, and I made an appetizer and this dessert! It was so much fun to have this delicious meal come together with everyones help. Everyone had one thing in mind: what does Dad like? That is exactly what inspired this dessert. I wanted to create something summery that my dad would love. Mission accomplished! Blueberry and lemon is a classic flavor combo that we all love. These bars were easy to make and were a great summer treat. They taste even better the next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graham CrackerCrust &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup graham crackers - crushed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ stick butter - melted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cream Cheese Layer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 8oz packages of cream cheese - softened &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp vanilla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blueberry Pie Layer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint fresh blueberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the zest of 1 lemon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tsp cornstarch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set oven to 325.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the crust : either use a food processor to grind the graham crackers or you can place in a large bag and crush them. Melt the butter and mix the 2 together. Press the mixture into an 8 x 8 square baking dish. I usually spray my dish with PAM non-stick cooking spray to be safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the cream cheese layer : using a food processor or hand mixer, blend the ingredients together. Once blended until smooth, spread evenly on top of graham cracker crust. Place in the oven on 325 degrees for about 30 minutes, until cooked through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the bars are baking, make the blueberry filling. In a small saucepan, put blueberries, sugar, and lemon zest in. Heat for about 5 minutes until simmering. Then, add cornstarch and let the mixture simmer for about 5 more minutes until it starts to thicken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380839_1162620157087675_1078370118_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the pan comes out of the oven, let it cool slightly. Pour blueberry filling on top to cover the cream cheese layer. At this point, it is best to put in the fridge to chill. Once chilled, you can add more lemon zest on top. Cut the bars into squares and enjoy! We found that they were actually better the second day because everything had a chance to firm up. A great make-ahead summer dish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11335163_627231654124948_996940625_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/blueberry-cheesecake-bars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">20df2477-d14b-4daa-97a6-351b994a716d</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 01:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Tacos with Mango Salsa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11328330_1436884929951866_445870342_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is Taco Tuesday at the Bowser’s and shrimp is on the menu tonight! We love tacos in all shapes, flavors, and forms and have eaten our fair share. I like to switch it up, and use seafood and shrimp in tacos, instead of always pork or beef.  The shrimp come out a little spicy and very flavorful, with an added zing from some lime zest. The mango salsa is sweet and also a little spicy from the jalapeno. I like to buy the mangoes when they are on sale and leave them on my counter for a few days to ripen. Then I get to decide what to make with them! The best is just to eat them super ripe and juicy. I like the added crunch of the slaw and the creamy consistency is a nice balance to the taco. Make these for your next taco night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11327090_779461435508748_556561080_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shrimp&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb peeled and deveined shrimp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp cumin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp chili powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp garlic powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp paprika&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lime zest from 1 lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;corn or flour tortillas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salsa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 mango - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 jalapeno - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red onion - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red pepper - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slaw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ head cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lime &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful chopped cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the salsa: Mix ingredients and let the flavors mingle. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11272799_1452172171745662_1890611574_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Slaw: Mix the ingredients and let the flavors mingle. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the shrimp : Make sure shrimp are peeled and deveined. Lets be honest, I love it when they are available that way in the store, and even more when they are on sale, but that is not the norm. Set aside some time to prep the shrimp. Make sure shrimp are rinsed, drained, and pat them dry. Add the remaining ingredients from the list (cumin-salt) to the shrimp. At this point, you can let these marinate for a bit, or you can get ready to cook them up. They do not need long to marinate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11282789_786614401445554_1845796248_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have some options. You can pan fry the shrimp in 1-2 tsp of olive oil, which is what I did. You can also throw the shrimp on skewers and grill them, if the weather permits. I would prefer to grill the shrimp to get a nice char, but it has been raining all day. They are delicious either way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve, add a few shrimp to each tortilla and top with slaw and salsa. Dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11296754_1041953755832593_22856041_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/shrimp-tacos-with-mango-salsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">dcafd733-83ee-4866-894b-93a4ee700664</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 01:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flounder Puttanesca</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11325764_974861889221028_1373965387_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flounder! I must say, this is a new fish for me. It all started 2 weeks ago when my family and I went on a birthday dinner for my mom and I. Our birthdays are a month apart, so we settled on a date in the middle. We chose an Italian restaurant and the first special of the night was Flounder Puttanesca. I thought to myself - “I will definitely not be having that, I am not even sure if I like flounder”. My brother decided to order that special and after tasting all of the meals, we unanimously voted his meal as the best meal of the night! There you have it, try new things and they may become new favorites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Puttanesca sauce is not even something I have often, but it really is simple and delicious. It has a nice salty, briny flavor. I was able to recreate this dish pretty easily and I wanted to share it because it is easy enough for a weeknight meal, but also special enough for a dinner party. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one ingredient I would like to address - the anchovies. I think some people may be opposed to trying this in the recipe, but I want to assure you that it will not give the sauce a “fishy” taste. What it will do, is give the sauce an added saltiness and really compliment the flounder. The anchovies basically melt into the sauce and there are not large pieces or bites. You will basically not even know they are in there. I would advise you to try them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11326400_1593491014265099_2049629446_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 flounder fillets, or approximately 1 pound&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup flour, for dusting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;canola oil for frying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large can whole peeled tomatoes (28 oz)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup pitted kalamata olives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;anchovies packed in oil - 4-5 small fillets &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 oz capers, ~ 3 tbsp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 garlic cloves, grated or minced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp red pepper flakes (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb pasta - your choice, we used angel hair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remove flounder and dry the fillets. Add salt and pepper to both sides and then dip each fillet into the flour. You want a light dusting on the fish. Add canola oil to a heavy bottomed pan about an inch up the side. You want to do a shallow fry and not submerge the whole fish in oil. My fillets were pretty thin, so they only needed 3 minutes per side. When you remove them from the oil, put them on a paper-towel lined plate to soak any excess oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add olive oil to a skillet over medium low heat.  Add in the sardine fillets and let them cook in the oil. Using a wooden spoon, break them apart. They will melt into the oil and sauce and you will not have chunks in there after a few minutes.  Add in the garlic and let everything cook for a minute.  Add in capers and cook for another minute. Next, use your hands to crush the whole tomatoes as you add them into the pan. This way, you will have smaller, bite-sized chunks of tomatoes in the sauce. Let the sauce come to a simmer to incorporate all the flavors. After a few minutes, add in the red pepper flakes (if using) and the calamata olives. The sauce doesn’t need to cook much after this, but I would simmer it for a few minutes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11327119_885127478212681_946569875_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, you can add the pasta into the sauce to mingle. Or, if you prefer, you can serve the pasta topped with sauce, then the fish on top of that and more sauce to finish. I added the pasta into the sauce then served it with a piece of fish on top and more sauce over the whole dish. It was really delicious, fresh, salty, and wonderful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11247676_1631879270382925_89241324_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manjia!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1bd99e70-9087-4bfd-88d4-33ea2694c6a4</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spinach Poppy Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-atl.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11243850_366276456900133_308885176_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to start by saying that I am sorry for posting another salad recipe this soon, but I absolutely have to share this one! Plus, it’s spring-time and I think we all can use a little more salad in our lives. This dressing is a real winner.  It is sweet, savory, and salty, with a nice bite from the onion.  The ingredients go nicely together and really compliment and balance each other. This salad makes a great lunch or side for dinner. I think it would also be lovely at a BBQ as a light and fresh option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, of course you can tweak the salad ingredients to use what you have and what you like. That is what I always do, and that is what inspired this salad! Hope you enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;spinach leaves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup cooked whole wheat pasta (optional - I used leftovers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sliced strawberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup of crumbled feta - to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful roasted sunflower seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poppy Seed Dressing &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup white vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp white sugar &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp grated white onion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp poppy seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 heaping tbsp dijon mustard &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by making the dressing. Add the sugar to the vinegar and whisk until sugar is dissolved, about 2 minutes. Next, add grated onion - I use a regular box grater on the large holes to do this. This will give you the onion flavor without the sharp bite. Add the dijon mustard and then the olive oil and whisk until emulsified. Add the poppy seeds at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the spinach and pasta to a large bowl and continue to add each layer on top. Mix with dressing and serve with extra sunflower seeds on top for a little added crunch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11252886_691378404342000_1821008213_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/spinach-poppy-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0d1023ff-0228-4151-baf5-0c2f50e248d3</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farro with Mushrooms</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11236294_832794346756139_1889030388_n.jpg" alt="Farro with Mushrroms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a great little side dish! Let me start by telling you about farro. It is one of my new favorite grains! The thing that I love about it is its texture and its chewiness. In my opinion, it is more interesting than quinoa and couscous. Don’t get me wrong - I love those as well, but quinoa is lacking texture and couscous can just be boring sometimes.  That is where farro comes in - to spice things up!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The definition of farro, straight from the wikipedia article is : “a food composed of the grains of certain wheat species. The exact definition is debated.” So you’ll just have to trust me and try it yourself! I find it in my local supermarket with the rice and the grains, but you can sometimes find it in the bulk bins of certain health food stores.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have been experimenting with it lately, and it can really stand up to most “dressings” and ingredients. Here, I tried to make it a savory side to go with the salmon and asparagus we were having for dinner.  The garlic butter is fantastic and really soaks into the farro. Who doesn’t love garlic butter slathered on anything and everything?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, I want to take some time to talk about the mushrooms. Mushrooms can be a finicky ingredient if not prepared properly. After some testing around, I think I have found a delicious way to bring out their flavor. Just want to give a shout-out to my friend Kelly for helping me perfect this technique. More on that below…&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups farro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cups low sodium chicken stock&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups water&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 package mushrooms - any kind you like&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ stick of butter&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cloves of garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup cooking sherry - available in the supermarket&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by bringing the chicken stock and water to boil in a medium sauce pan. I like to always use low sodium chicken stock so I can control the amount of salt in the recipe. Once boiling, add in farro and some salt. You can adjust this later if you didn't add enough. One thing about farro, is that all the liquid does not have to evaporate like it does for rice. Most of the time, you have to drain the farro at the end of cooking it. After you add the farro in, reduce the heat to a simmer and put a lid on it. It will need to cook about 30 minutes until tender but still chewy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11241894_890291644363578_507844597_n.jpg" alt="Farro with Mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the farro is cooking , slice your mushrooms if they are not already sliced and heat a saute pan on medium high heat. Put the mushrooms in the pan DRY. No oil, no salt, nothing to begin with. Mushrooms have liquid in them, and when you salt them early, they get watery. Give the mushrooms a few minutes to soften, then they will release liquid for a few minutes and dry up and begin to stick to the pan. At this point, after about 10 minutes, add in the sherry and let the mushrooms cook until they are dry again. Add in salt and a good dose of fresh cracked black pepper. Set aside until farro is done.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a small saucepan, heat the butter and grate in your garlic using a microplane. You could also just mince finely. Let them melt together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Drain your farro, place it in a bowl, and then pour the hot garlic butter over top. Smells so good! Top the bowl with the sauted mushrooms and dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11274374_1444262582551457_1082559282_n.jpg" alt="Farro with mushrooms"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/farro-with-mushrooms/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">4b2cbaa9-d656-4a84-9dba-52f786c1085c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 18 May 2015 00:59:31 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mango Slaw</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-iad.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11243878_724515674325519_703809639_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is the slaw I served alongside the double bean burgers I posted earlier this week. It is so perfect for the grilling season and will be a great accompaniment to your BBQ’s.  It comes together in no-time and all the ingredients are fresh. I have a feeling this will be on a regular rotation through the spring and summer cook-out season. It is crunchy, tangy, and sweet from the mango. What more could you ask for?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;  
  &lt;li&gt;1/4 cup greek yogurt&lt;/li&gt;    
  &lt;li&gt;¼ cup mayo&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;lime juice - 1/2 a lime&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp dijon&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;1 tsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;* ½ tsp celery seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ small green cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ small red cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 ripe mango - peeled and sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red pepper - sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*I used ½ tsp of celery salt, so I omitted any extra salt. If you use plain celery seed, you may still need to add a pinch of salt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, make the dressing. Combine all the ingredients, mix, and taste for seasoning.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Chop and slice all your veggies and mango. Add in dressing and put it in the fridge so the flavors can meld. I did not use all the dressing. I would start with half, and then adjust from there. Sometimes, after it sits a while, it soaks up dressing and you need to add more later, so save some.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11263295_1600953910175582_460942730_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is really a perfect side dish for any BBQ, burgers, grilled chicken, seafood, and everything! The best part is, it gets better the longer it sits, so it is a perfect make-ahead dish.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You’ll want to save this recipe for your upcoming summer BBQ’s!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/mango-slaw/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">ef8de63e-52da-4cd0-b2bb-086529d7cc5c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 15 May 2015 00:54:35 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Double Bean Burgers</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11232777_669494849850530_228232587_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burger"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My husband and I can both agree - my black bean burger game has come a LONG way! I have been “attempting” to make non-mushy black bean burgers for years now, and I am happy to say that I have finally mastered it! I’m sure many of you have tried to make some form of bean burgers and they have not been the consistency you were hoping for. I have tried pan frying, baking, and even grilling. I would not try grilling, trust me. However, I have had great success in the combination of freezing the burgers, baking the burgers on high heat, then broiling them, which gives you a “burger-like” consistency and can stand up on a bun.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are so great because they are an awesome meat free option, very filling, and you can play around with the ingredients and toppings to make what you like. I used a mixture of black beans and cannellini beans because I think the cannellini beans are so smooth and creamy that they balance out the black beans. You can add more or less spice with the jalapenos and chili powder. The toppings I used really compliment the black bean burger nicely, but the sky's the limit! &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The chipotle mayo is so smoky and a bit spicy, the avocado is cool and creamy, and the sprouts are a fun and fresh twist. I do not usually use spouts in my cooking, but I love them when I eat them out. I saw them in my supermarket and scooped them right up for this recipe. I plan on using them top top sandwiches and wraps for the next week or 2.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make these for your next meatless Monday or for your vegetarian friend!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Burgers&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cans black beans - rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 can cannellini beans - rinsed and drained&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large jalapeno, seeds removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red bell pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cloves of garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 egg&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1  cup panko bread crumbs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 1/2 tsp ground cumin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½-1 tsp chili powder (if you like spice)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixins'&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;hamburger buns&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;avocado&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;greens&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;red onion&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chipotle mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mayo&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup mayo or light mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tsp chipotles in adobo (I use the juice and not the actual peppers - can adjust to spice level)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, give the peppers, garlic, and cilantro a rough dice. Toss them into the food processor and pulse until they are diced fine. Drain and rinse the beans and add them to a large bowl. Using your hands, get in there and “smoosh” the beans up. Of course you can use a fork if you’d like, but my grandmother always said - “a cook’s best tools are her hands.” She still cooks that way today. Add the food processor mix to the beans.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, add the seasoning and taste. This is your chance to taste before you add the egg. Add in the egg and mix to combine the mixture.  Add panko bread crumbs and stir. These should soak up some of the excess liquid and make the mixture more dry. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11256826_504694216349926_863440241_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, I form my beans into burger patties on parchment paper or a silpat baking mat. Put the burgers into the freezer to firm up for about 1/2 hour - 1 hour.  Preheat the oven to 400 degrees.  You can take the burgers straight from the freezer to the oven.  Bake the burgers for 20 minutes on 400 degrees then put them on the broil setting for 3-5 minutes to crisp up the tops.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the mayo, just mix the 2 together and save for the topping.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11251145_842855302453170_841597462_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve, add your burger to the bun, top with chipotle mayo, red onion, avocado, and alfalfa sprouts. I served mine alongside my mango slaw, which I will post later this week. Stay tuned...&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11236410_626942004108157_1412163059_n.jpg" alt="Double Bean Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/double-bean-burgers/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">03b07877-7d67-49d5-b4c1-ad29291b1096</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:49:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Pil-Pil</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11192926_1390312407962346_2082094703_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Pil-Pil"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is my take on one of my favorite appetizers, served at a quaint little Greek restaurant that we used to live by. Since we lived across the street, we frequented &lt;a href="http://www.dmitrisrestaurant.com/2nd.html"&gt;Dimitris&lt;/a&gt; numerous times, and always ended up with this appetizer since we loved it so much.  What we know : it’s spicy, it’s garlicky, and it is crispy and delicious. I think I came pretty close to recreating this recipe on the first try.  Before writing this, I did a quick google search and learned that this a common tapas recipe from Spain, called Gambas al Ajillo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since returning from our trip to the islands of Belize, I have been craving seafood. On the islands, it is so easy because it is always the fresh catch of the day. I ate fish and seafood every night and loved it. I have been inspired to try more fish dishes and experiment with new types of fish and seafood. I hope to have some new and exciting fish dishes coming up in the near future.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 serrano chile, diced fine (can sub jalapeno)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ lb of shrimp - peeled and deveined&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;5 cloves of garlic, minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 scallion, chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ teaspoon red pepper flakes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cilantro - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ ¼ cup flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;squeeze of lemon, optional&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To begin, make sure shrimp are cleaned and patted until completely dry. Add salt and pepper to shrimp and then dunk them in the flour, covering all sides with a light coat. Next prepare your veg. Dice the chile, garlic, and scallion.  Add oil to the pan and let it sizzle. Add in just the chile and scallion and let it cook for about 3 minutes. Add your dredged shrimp and let it cook and crisp up. It can take about 3-5 minutes per side, depending on the size of your shrimp. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11184474_2030452110427040_1049964850_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Pil-Pil"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;After you flip the shrimp, add the garlic in. Garlic has a tendency to burn, so we want to prevent this by adding it later. Once the shrimp is almost done, toss everything together in the pan. Add in chili flakes and cilantro and let the flavors marry. Make sure you scrape up all the bits of flavor from the bottom of the pan. Serve with a squeeze of lemon, and even grilled bread to sop up the excess!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/shrimp-pil-pil/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">cb68552e-3f46-4725-b47a-b16eb4158bd2</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 01:36:21 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Chicken Ka-pita-bobs</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11190989_850501015016073_1897984115_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I know what you are thinking - Is it a kabob or a pita? Well I thought it would be fun to turn the chicken kabobs into a Greek/Lebanese style pita with tzatziki! It spices up your chicken routine and you can make it on the grill. I want to say grilling season is here for good, but who knows with this weather! Hopefully it will turn around in May. Once we start grilling outside, we grill straight through until winter hits. It is so nice to be outside grilling, plus it is less dishes!  &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This recipe is just a basic and easy marinade. As for the veggies, you can use what you like, I just used onions this time. The tzatziki recipe is actually not my own. I know I am Lebanese and I am positive my gram has a spectacular recipe for this, but I have been making Ina Garten’s recipe for years, and it is just too good to change. It is utterly perfect and we love it every time. I will post a link to it so you can check it out. You can top these pitas with tomatoes, onions, pickles, anything you like. They are healthy and delicious way to jump out of that grilled chicken rut!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Kabobs&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 pounds of chicken breasts or tenders, cut into 1 inch cubes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lemon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 garlic cloves, minced or grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoons fresh dill&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt and pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large white onion, cut into chunks&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;skewers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pitas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;pitas, I used whole wheat&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;fixins : tomatoes, red onions&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&lt;a href="http://www.foodnetwork.com/recipes/ina-garten/easy-tzatziki-with-toasted-pita-crisps-recipe.html"&gt;Tzatziki&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I find that if I take the extra time out to marinate the chicken, it comes out juicier in the end.  Chop the chicken into equal size cubes and place in a large ziplock bag or in a dish to marinate. Add in a good amount of salt and pepper, then the oil, lemon juice, garlic, and dill.  Marinate for at least 3 hours but up to an entire day. Once chicken is marinated, grab your skewers and thread the chicken and the white onion (or veggies), alternating. Grill the skewers until the chicken is cooked through to 165 degrees. Let them rest while you prepare the pitas, tzatziki and toppings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11203505_350166058514532_1557411626_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the pita, add a skewer of chicken meat and onions, top with tzatziki and veggies! This recipe can really be adapted to the veggies and toppings you want, so have fun with it.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11193173_1079468495402124_2135805408_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Ka-pita-bobs"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/chicken-ka-pita-bobs/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">484575d0-3eee-430d-b706-f31a59139fda</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 00:25:22 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
