<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>Bare Bones Cooking</title><description>Fresh. Seasonal. Delicious.</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/</link><generator>Ghost 0.5</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 10:36:44 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://barebonescooking.com/rss/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><ttl>60</ttl><item><title>Garlic Mussels in White Wine</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11875356_1483405778621294_635288868_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is a simple, delicious, and fresh meal. Mussels are something that most people probably only eat when they are out at a restaurant. However, they could not be easier to make at home! Whenever I see mussels on sale, I snatch them up. This meal comes together in under 30 minutes and can be served as an appetizer or a meal on its own.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 leek (only white part) - sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 cloves of garlic - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup white wine (can use chicken broth instead)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lemon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bag mussels - 2 lbs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cleaned, rinsed, beard removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;crusty bread for dipping&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mussel Prep:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you get your mussels, sometimes they involve some prep on your part. The first thing I do is remove them from the bag and run them under cold water. Scrub them it make sure you get the grit off of the outside. Also, mussels have a “beard” which is a stingy bunch that hang on the outside of the shell. Sometimes these are removed, sometimes you have to remove them. This is an important step because they can be gritty and add an unpleasant taste to the sauce and the mussels. Once the mussels are cleaned, add them to a large bowl and cover with ice and set the in the refrigerator until you are ready to use them.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Leek Prep:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Since leeks grow in the dirt, they involve some extra prep work to make sure they are clean before you add them to your meal. You only use the white stems of the leeks, so chop off the large leafy tops and discard them. Then, slice the leeks into thin rounds and add them to large bowl with water. As you add them, separate the rings to be sure you get the dirt out of the rings. Submerge the leeks in water and let them sit for a little bit to be sure the dirt all falls to the bottom. Then drain them over a strainer and rinse one last time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11849845_877694392299600_1068477572_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Mince your garlic, open your wine, and slice your lemon. At this point, the meal comes together in under 10 minutes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add about 2 tablespoons of olive oil and 2 tablespoons of butter into a heavy bottomed large pot. Add the leeks and saute for 5-7 minutes until soft. Add in the garlic and cook for 30 seconds. Next, add in the white wine and let it cook until reduced by half, about 5 minutes. Ad din mussels and give the pan a big shake a few times to mix everything. Add the lid and let the mussels steam about 3-5 minutes depending on the size. Once they are all open, they are done!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11820626_1675658039312721_374310930_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I like to transfer the mussels to a large bowl, add a squeeze of lemon and serve with toasted, crispy garlic bread for all that delicious sauce.&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/garlic-mussels-in-white-wine/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0eab8ea7-dfb5-443d-8020-0a7358150d2e</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 09 Sep 2015 01:03:26 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Grilled Shrimp Po' Boys</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11349390_1874124519478439_1632843067_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I love a good po’ boy sandwich, who doesn’t? However, especially in the summer, you don’t want a heavy deep fried sandwich, so I thought I would try and lighten things up a bit. Still all the same great po’ boy flavor, minus most of the fat! BY grilling the shrimp, you get a great flavor on them and a nice little char. This is a really quick meal that can come together in snap. The shrimp do not need any time to marinate and the sauce is just simply mixing everything together. This is great to make on a nice summer evening with a nice cold beverage. Hope you enjoy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shrimp&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ lb peeled and deveined shrimp (the bigger, the better)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 1-2 tsp cajun seasoning&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 1 tsp chili powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remoulade&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tsp dijon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp worchestire&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp tabasco&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp horseradish&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 clove garlic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp paprika&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gherkins - ¼ cup chopped fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp lemon juice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a pinch of salt and pepper &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Fixins’&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lettuce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;rolls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start by preparing your shrimp. Make sure they are peeled, deveined, and rinsed. Then pat them dry and add the seasonings. You can go heavy on the cajun seasoning and light on the chili powder, unless you want to spice things up. It is such a simple seasoning, which such a huge flavor. I find it easier to skewer the shrimp that way they are easier to cook on the grill. If you are cooking them in a skillet, there is no need to skewer them. They will only take a few minutes on each side to cook. Note : this definitely varies and depends on the size you choose. They had very large shrimp on sale when I made these, so mine took about 5 minutes on each side until they were cooked through. The bigger the shrimp, the more texture and flavor you get.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11821294_408922982633667_527324756_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the sauce: mix together the ingredients and let the flavors come together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make sure you have good rolls for the sandwiches. Bread can make or break a sandwich! To assemble, cut the roll and scoop some of the bread filling out to make room. Add the shrimp, remoulade, lettuce, and tomato. These sandwiches are messy and amazingly delicious. Perfect for a summer night outdoors :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/t51.2885-15/10948826_1608240659464321_1041226196_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/grilled-shrimp-po-boys-2/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">83826ced-f53c-42a4-9c9a-9143f97b7b65</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 23 Aug 2015 01:15:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Farmers Market Vegetable Lasagna</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11910449_665803513554646_1237185443_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If there is one more homemade and delicious meal you make this summer, let this be it! This lasagna takes the bounty of delicious produce that summer has to offer and lets it shine. There is no pasta. There is no meat. There is not even any sauce. It is vegetable lasagna and the vegetables rule.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Due to my hectic work schedule and the fact that I work every other weekend, I realized I had not had a chance to head to my favorite farmers market,  &lt;a href="http://thefoodtrust.org/farmers-markets/market/headhouse"&gt;Headhouse Farmers' Market&lt;/a&gt;. Due to Nate’s unfortunate luck on his bicycle last Sunday, we both found ourselves free around 11 am and got to go to the market together. Let me tell you this - the farmers market was kickin’! It was packed, they added even more vendors, and the produce was all fresh, ripe, and abundant. It was fantastic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have had this idea in my mind for some time now, but did not have any of the logistics set. I set out down the aisle of the farmers market to see what looked best and I would take it from there. The fruit was exceptional and we stocked up on that. The tomatoes were all different colors, shapes, and sizes. I got so many different tomatoes that I decided to use fresh, ripe tomatoes as the “sauce”. The squash, eggplants, and peppers were freshly picked and brightly colored. When we returned home, I had a cornucopia of fresh produce to turn into a delicious Sunday Night Dinner. There is something about cooking a long and lavish meal on a Sunday to end the week on a great note and get ready for the upcoming week ahead.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xap1/t51.2885-15/11201580_1051113171585935_252672865_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is certainly not a quick meal (what lasagna ever is?). It is certainly not a meal I would recommend making outside of the season. The reason this works is because the vegetables are at their peak ripeness and the tomatoes are bursting with flavor. I also find it refreshing to have comfort food like this with a seasonal twist. It has all the comfort of lasagna, but will not weigh you down. And that is what summer cooking is all about!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ingredients &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 yellow squash&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 zucchini&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 eggplants&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 red or yellow peppers&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4-5 large ripe tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful fresh basil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mozzarella cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Filling&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;16 oz ricotta cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 garlic cloves - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 eggs - lightly beaten&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bag sauted spinach (will wilt down to about ¼ cup)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prep :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The eggplant will take the longest to prep, so start with that. Slice the eggplant in long planks. In order to remove the bitter flavor, salt the eggplant on one side and place it in a strainer or on a cookie sheet to drain. Let it drain on one side for about 20-30 minutes. Then, flip it and re-salt and let the other side drain. Lay a kitchen towel down and dry each side of the eggplant to remove all the moisture. Brush the eggplant with olive oil and sprinkle on some black pepper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11849177_129861827356482_701903382_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the peppers, you will roast them. Char them on the grill until black all around, Then, place them in a brown pepper bag to sweat. After 20 minutes, remove the black part to reveal the roasted pepper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the zucchini and squash, slice them in planks, relatively the same size. Then brush them with olive oil, and sprinkle salt and pepper.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the tomatoes, slice them into thick rounds and sprinkle them with salt. This will take the place of a traditional “sauce”, so it is important to have juicy and ripe tomatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11296905_468318970020283_760709327_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the filling, begin by sauteing the spinach in a little olive oil with salt and pepper. Then, mix everything together and set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Grill the eggplant, zucchini, squash. Slice the peppers and get everything set.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11428689_1163332083682548_1499253459_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Assembly:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set oven to 350 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11899706_162092424123435_922243921_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once all the veggies are prepped, start the assembly. Using a 13 by 9 inch pan - drizzle olive oil on the bottom. Here are the layers :&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;eggplant // ricotta cheese mix // tomato // basil &lt;br&gt;
zucchini // ricotta cheese mix  //tomato // basil &lt;br&gt;
squash // ricotta cheese mix //tomato // basil &lt;br&gt;
mozzarella cheese // peppers // parmesan cheese&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11821843_1463876140604804_1188180927_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cover the lasagna in foil and bake it for 30 minutes. Then remove the foil and broil it for 3-5 minutes until the cheese starts to bubble. Serve with toasted baguette to sop up the juices.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11910290_948864301822521_2078922205_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you all will take the time to hit the farmers market or farm stand and enjoy the flavors summer had to offer!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/farmers-market-veggie-lasagna/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">7a6f3f30-df97-4874-b35d-75e9f13d52a8</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 20 Aug 2015 17:00:39 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Meatless Monday : Stuffed Peppers and Tomatoes</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xap1/t51.2885-15/10431984_924255094308459_942383448_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hello again! Sorry for my brief hiatus; vacation, work, and summer got the best of me for a little bit. However, I have a bunch of great recipes lined up and ready to go and a few more tricks up my sleeve before summer is over. These stuffed peppers and tomatoes are really great for any season, but the tomatoes are at their peak right now.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You will certainly not miss the meat in these hearty stuffed peppers and tomatoes. We like to eat meatless around here at least once a week and I find it especially easier in the summer when the veggies are abundant and fresh. Since it is the heart of summer and the tomatoes are perfect and ripe, I decided to stuff half peppers and half tomatoes. The peppers are firmer and tasty and the tomatoes are juicy and sweet. This is a great combo for a summer dinner. The quinoa and the beans add a lot of protein to the meal, so you will be full and satisfied. These will also make great leftovers, you can easily double the ingredients and make more!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11337217_615454451891071_969652403_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Meatless Stuffed Peppers and Tomatoes&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup red onion - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 ear of cooked corn - kernels removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 can black beans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 jalapeno - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup shredded cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup quinoa&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red bell pepper - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup enchilada sauce - split into 2 parts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 scallion - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sour cream for serving&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by cooking your quinoa. The ratio here is 2:1. 1/2 cup quinoa and 1 cup of liquid (water or broth). Bring to a boil and then simmer for 15-20 minutes until all liquid is absorbed. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, saute peppers and onion for about 5 minutes just to soften. Add a pinch of salt and pepper to the mix. Set aside. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11372140_1021984161153804_769180381_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a large bowl, add quinoa, peppers/onions, corn kernels, black beans, and cheese. Mix everything together, then add ½ cup of enchilada sauce. Let the flavors mix while you prep your peppers and tomatoes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Preheat the oven to 350 degrees.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hollow out the peppers but removing the stem and the inside seeds and ribs. As for the tomatoes, use a small pairing knife to cut around the top, remove the stem, and scoop out the seeds and the insides. Usually when I make stuffed peppers, the thing that bothers me is that the peppers do not fully cook in the amount of time that everything else does, leaving you with a semi-crunchy pepper. Well, I have a new-found tip for solving this problem. Boil just the peppers in water for approximately 5 minutes to soften them. Then drain them and place them into the dish to stuff. Note: you do not need to do this with the tomatoes as they will cook just fine in the oven.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11252736_907190546020291_866271730_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once everything is ready, stuff the peppers and tomatoes to the top with the mixture. Push down to fit as much as you can. Pour the remaining ½ cup of enchilada sauce on the bottom of the dish to keep them moist. Cover everything tightly in foil and bake on 350 degrees for 10 minutes. After 10 minutes, remove from the oven, add cheese on top and bake for another 15 minutes until done. You can broil them for 1-2 minutes at the end if you want to cheese to get bubbly!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11257081_844918182245107_472747972_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These are perfect for meatless monday - healthy and filling!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/meatless-monday-stuffed-peppers-and-tomatoes/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">381f4e12-2273-42ef-8272-de51b9fa21a0</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 16 Aug 2015 17:59:08 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Mahi-mahi with Mango Salsa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11312553_1614697472125027_1449796634_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto;  width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone! I wanted to post this fish for you all because it was a fairly new fish to me. It is definitely not a fish I can say I’ve ever cooked at home. I may have eaten it out before, but really was not sure of how it would taste prepared on the grill. Well, I can tell you this: it is a hearty, meaty, and delicious fish. It is substantial and very filling. It is mild and tastes fresh. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When I think of Mahi-Mahi I think of Hawaiian flavors. I thought the mango salsa would pair perfectly and it really did. It added a burst of bright flavor to each bite. The jalapeno spiced things up, the lime juice balanced out the sweetness of the mango and the red pepper was a nice crunch. This salsa would really pair well with any fish. Grilling the fish was a nice option because it infused some flavor into the fish and it cooked in no time. No pans to wash = happy Kristina. I hope you will all take my advice and try something new this summer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Fish&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb Mahi-Mahi&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 2 tablespoons of olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;juice of ½ a lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 garlic cloves - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 1 teaspoon salt, and fresh cracked black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Mango Salsa&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 mango - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ red pepper - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup red onion - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 jalapeno - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful of cilantro - diced  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;juice of ½ a lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;a pinch of salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Start by marinating the fish. Pat the fish dry, add the olive oil then salt and pepper and rub all over the fish. Then add the garlic and lime juice and let the fish marinate for half an hour. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next, make your salsa. Once everything is diced, add it all to a bowl and then add a pinch of salt and the juice of half a lime. Taste for seasonings. The longer the salsa sits, the better.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11420732_878118588948992_1931935893_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto; width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the fish is ready, heat your grill to medium. Make sure to oil the grates before adding the fish so it doesn’t stick. Add the fish onto the grill, skin side down. Let the fish cook about 5 minutes. When you are ready to flip the fish, make sure it pulls away from the grill easily. If not, wait a little longer. The fish will tell you when it’s ready :) Cook the fish on the other side for 5-7 minutes until done. We used a thermometer to tell when it was finished cooking. The internal temperature should read 140 degrees. The fish should be firm to the touch and cooked through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is really easy for a weeknight meal, it comes together in a snap! We served the the fish on a bed of coconut rice with a side of grilled corn. Sweet summer meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/t51.2885-15/1517234_953337674718075_183386894_n.jpg" style="margin: 0 auto; width: 680px"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/mahi-mahi-with-mango-salsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">366abd72-4b47-406d-ade9-7c76126ce9f1</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2015 00:18:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Greek Panzanella Chicken</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfp1/t51.2885-15/10005682_1470147496633847_148176965_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here it is : the perfect summer meal! I know I have been saying this a lot, but this truly is it. It is fresh, light, healthy, and absolutely delicious. It comes together in no time and some can be made ahead of time. We are now into the perfect time of year where the tomatoes are bursting with flavor and they really shine here. The feta cheese is salty and goes perfectly with the greek salad dressing. The bread cubes are the best part; they are crunchy and they soak in all the great juices. We devoured this for dinner, each bite better as the salad sits and gains flavor. The salad portion of this meal is so good that you could even serve it as a dinner on its own!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cucumber - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large tomato - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 red onion - sliced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup kalamata olives - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 block feta cheese - rough chop&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;baguette bread cubes - toasted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chicken thighs or chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Greek Dressing (adapted from Ina Garten’s recipe on foodnetwork)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 cloves garlic, grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoon dried oregano&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon Dijon mustard&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 cup red wine vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 teaspoon salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 teaspoon freshly ground black pepper&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*Note: the dressing recipe is doubled as I listed it. If you are making the salad alone, cut it in half. I used half of the dressing for the chicken and half for the salad.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Make the dressing first. You will mix together the ingredients, then separate it equally in half. It makes a little less than 2 cups, so about  ¾ cups each. Use half to marinate the chicken. I marinated mine for a few hours, but the longer the better with chicken. Set the other dressing aside for later.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Prep all of your veggies : cucumber, tomato, red onion, olives, and feta. Add them to a large bowl and pour some of the dressing over them to begin marinating. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11424917_529247130564671_1601084377_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add your chicken to the grill or skillet and cook until finished.  While chicken is cooking, cut your baguette into large cubes. Add a thin layer of olive oil to a pan and crisp up the bread slices. They will only take 3-4 minutes per side.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11356358_1088011741228190_2034377552_n.jpg" alt="Greek Panzanella CHicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Pull your chicken off the heat and let it rest. Add the bread cubes to the salad and toss the remaining dressing over the bread and mix.  To serve : put the chicken on the bottom of the plate and pile it high with the salad! This is the true taste of summer :)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xpa1/t51.2885-15/10731680_1612132175717606_1091750465_n.jpg" alt="Chicken Panzanella Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had the salad leftover the next day; the only thing you have to do is make new bread cubes because they will get soggy. The rest of the salad is even better the next day!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/greek-panzanella-chicken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">968bc3b3-bc22-4e3d-bf29-d3a009476565</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jul 2015 19:50:47 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>BBQ Burgers with Arugula and Crispy Shallots</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xpa1/t51.2885-15/11202919_499437283548103_217523149_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These burgers are a great treat! Sometimes it is so nice and comforting to make your own fancy burgers at home on the grill.  You can cook them how you like them and the topping possibilities are endless. I just made these beauties for Sunday night dinner after a weekend of working. It was the perfect cap to end the weekend. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I wanted to do something a little different and play with some topping ideas and flavor combos. These flavors compliment each other perfectly for a truly amazing burger. There are 2 types of burger making styles. The type where you add ingredients into the meat mixture and keep the toppings basic. Or the type where you keep the burger meat plain and make the toppings count. My husband and I are more into making the latter version. We keep our burger meat simple with a good dose of salt and fresh cracked black pepper and we let the toppings shine through. You can taste the delicious, juicy meat and the toppings really help to round out the flavor of each bite. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;These burgers are first topped with gruyere cheese which is arguably one of the most delicious melty cheeses and perfect as a burger topper. I took shallots and sliced them thin, threw them in some flour, and shallow fried them in vegetable oil for a great salty crunch. The sauce is genius - equal parts of mayo and BBQ sauce for a creamy and tangy bite. The arugula is peppery and helps to offset the sweet BBQ sauce. Together, this makes for the perfect burger bite!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I hope you will make these before summer ends, I promise they will not disappoint! The nice thing is that you can adapt this recipe to feed just 2 people or a whole party of people easily.  They come together quick and will definitely be memorable. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb ground meat (for 4 - or you can adjust for more or less)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;burger buns of your choice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;gruyere cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup of arugula&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 shallots, sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup flour - for dredging&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;~ 1 cup vegetable oil for shallow frying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup favorite BBQ sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by prepping your ingredients. The shallots will take the most time and prep. Heat the vegetable oil on medium heat on the stove until just before boiling.  Peel the shallots and slice them into thin rounds. Add them into the flour and lightly coat them. Once the oil is ready, drop some into the oil, but do not crowd the pan. I did these in about 3 batches. Shallow fry the shallots until brown and crispy. Once finished, add them to a paper-towel lined plate to catch the drippings. Salt them immediately after removing from the oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11352065_432081840308354_1696740413_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set the shallots aside. Get the arugula ready by washing and drying the leaves and set them aside as while. For the sauce, mix together BBQ sauce and mayo.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xpa1/t51.2885-15/10809512_114169242258059_1936482464_n.jpg" alt="BBQ burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the burgers, add salt and pepper to the meat and mix with your hands quickly. Form the burgers into patties based on the size you would like. Cook the burgers on medium heat on your grill until desired doneness. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I snagged this neat little chart from food network to give you their recommended cooking temperatures. You can always cut into it to check if you don’t have a thermometer, but I highly recommend using a meat thermometer for perfect cooking.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Beef : Food Network Recommendation &lt;br&gt;
Rare = 125 + 3 minute rest &lt;br&gt;
Medium Rare = 130-135 &lt;br&gt;
Medium = 135-140 &lt;br&gt;
Medium Well = 140-150 &lt;br&gt;
Well = 155 + &lt;br&gt;
Ground = 160&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When burgers are almost done, add cheese so it melts. Toast buns on grill, if desired.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To assemble burgers : Add meat/cheese to the bun, then add arugula, then shallots, and the BBQ mayo on the top. Dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11425273_761502367308824_924565761_n.jpg" alt="BBQ Burgers"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/bbq-burgers-with-arugula-and-crispy-shallots/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">8b799846-6953-4021-a18a-9109fc76191c</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 13 Jul 2015 21:20:32 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11333344_1581127745481976_72603921_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;During the summer months, we all have so many occasions that could use a great side dish like this pasta salad. There are holidays like the 4th of July that just passed, BBQ’s, potlucks, and picnics. This is such a fun spin on pasta salad and it has a lighter feel. I usually use whole wheat pasta, which helps. I gave this salad a greek spin and used kalamata olives and feta cheese because they are salty and they compliment the sweet sun-dried tomato perfectly! The arugula has a nice sharp bite and also offsets any sweetness. All of these flavors go together so nicely and are truly the perfect compliment to any meal. It goes well with meat, fish, or can even be served alone as a light lunch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 oz sun-dried tomatoes ~ 10 pieces packed in oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup of the oil from the sun-dried tomato jar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup parmesan cheese&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup arugula &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ cup kalamata olives - pitted and chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup feta crumbles&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb pasta - I used whole wheat bowties&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can begin by cooking your pasta in a large pot of salted water. Cook to al dente and drain the pasta and let it cool just a little bit.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the “sauce”, begin by pulsing the sun-dried tomatoes in the food processor. I usually dump in about ¼ cup of the oil from the sun-dried tomato jar to thin it out a bit.  Next, add an additional ½ cup of regular olive oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11410370_127598627574059_1152604730_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once pasta has cooled, but is still a little warm, add the parmesan cheese and mix. Then add the sun-dried sauce you made. Allow this mixture to cool in the fridge until closer to the time you are ready to serve. This pasta salad is served cold or at room temperature. After the pasta salad has cooled, add in the arugula, feta crumbles, and kalamata olives. Mix and serve immediately or chill longer to let the flavors marry.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This salad is so perfect for BBQ’s or picnics because it can sit out and be served at any temperature. This recipe is a must before the end of the summer!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11335538_1459471921019984_1756114588_n.jpg" alt="Sun-dried Tomato Pasta Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/sun-dried-tomato-pasta-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">63cd5d33-850e-4ece-8ed4-89c57d28ee45</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 01:48:29 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Quesadillas</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380960_1582324645364771_2087409641_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My apologies for posting another shrimp recipe so soon, but it is just such a great summer option! It is an easily-attainable, pretty affordable seafood option. It is nice to switch up classics with new flavors. That is just what I did here. Most people think of chicken, beef, or pork in their quesadillas, but swapping out meat for seafood is a great alternative. The shrimp is bold and spicy, the corn is sweet and fresh, and the scallions and beans are great additions. When pressed together with gooey cheddar cheese, each bite is bursting with great flavors! These are fun to serve cut up as an appetizer with a side of sour cream and tomatoes. You can also have them as a main meal with a vegetable or rice side, which is what we did. This is a great summer meal!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Quesadillas&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1/2 lb peeled and deveined shrimp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;flour tortillas - 2 per quesadilla (this made 5)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;chipotle in adobo, just the sauce&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 corn cob - kernels removed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ can black beans&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 scallion - sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cheddar cheese - grated&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Toppings&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Pico : diced tomato, diced red onion, diced jalapeno, cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sour cream&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I started this off by marinating my shrimp for about half an hour while I was preparing other things. I dried off my shrimp, added salt and pepper, and brushed them with chipotle sauce. I elf the actual peppers in the can and just used the sauce. That gives plenty of spice! They do not need long to marinate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11357442_952477491483883_19807296_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the filling for the quesadillas, start by cooking the shrimp. I made them on my indoor grill. You can grill them or pan fry them, whatever is easiest. If they are small like mine were, they only need a few minutes in each side. Once cooked, add them to a medium sized bowl. To that bowl, add you cooked corn kernels, black beans and scallions. This will be you filling.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380797_1602504120028225_1804088040_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you have a panini or sandwich press, you can use this to press the quesadillas. If not, you can press them in a pan with a heavy pan on top. Add a tortilla to the bottom, add the filling leaving a small border around the edges and pile the cheese on top. Place another tortilla on top then close the lid and let it cook until the cheese is melted. Flip the tortilla carefully and let the other side cook until finished! You can serve these in a whole circle with a big dollop of sour cream and pico or you can cut them into wedges and top each wedge with the goodies. Delicious any which way you slice it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11423000_458400464321694_537719983_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Quesadillas"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/srimp-quesadillas/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">b76b5630-e963-49a9-94c7-df2ed039a9ca</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 01:23:14 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Poppin' Cherry Chicken</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11355866_410440285806013_615903290_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here we have a perfect summer meal. Summertime is the best time for tomatoes to shine. This recipe is my spin on the classic chicken parm. The chicken is crispy and flavorful. The spinach is healthy and garlicky. The tomatoes are sweet and burst with flavor in your mouth. The cheese on top is ooey and gooey and ties everything together. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We had this for Sunday dinner for my brother and his girlfriend. It was pretty fun to have extra hands in the kitchen to help with the prep. So bring your family, friends, and kids into the kitchen and make this before summer is over!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup flour&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cups bread crumbs ( I used seasoned)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;*6 thin sliced chicken breasts&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint cherry tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 oz fresh mozzarella&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 bag spinach &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 cloves of garlic - minced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;*the chicken must be sliced thin - if you buy the large chicken breasts, cut them in half lengthwise &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For this meal, I find it best to prep all of the parts and then assemble the chicken and bake.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the chicken breading : &lt;br&gt;
Begin by setting up your breading station. Add the flour, eggs, and breadcrumbs each into a separate container. Pat your chicken dry and add salt and pepper. Next, dip the chicken in flour, then into the egg, and finally into the breadcrumbs. Set on a late until you are ready to pan-fry. Once you are ready to cook, shallow fry each piece in enough olive oil to coat the pan. Since they are thin, they will cook quickly - 3-4 minutes per side. Once cooked, add to a paper towel to drain.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cherry Tomatoes : &lt;br&gt;
Add oil, salt, and pepper to tomatoes and roast on 350 degrees for 20 minutes. You want the tomatoes to be at the point where they just burst (see below).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11326823_457678617737930_203090873_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Spinach : &lt;br&gt;
Saute in olive oil to wilt the spinach down. After about 5-7 minutes when it is cooked, add a pinch of salt and pepper and the minced garlic.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11410616_1598583070403518_491274640_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Dish : &lt;br&gt;
Take a piece of chicken and add the spinach on top. Next, add the cherry tomatoes and mozzarella cheese.  Since everything is already cooked at this point, we just want to melt the cheese. Put your oven on the broil setting and broil the chicken on the top rack for 2-3 minutes until cheese is melted and bubbly.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11376712_826271174128146_223030176_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I served this alongside a simple pasta with the rest of the roasted tomatoes from the prep, roasted garlic, and parmesan cheese.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11356000_828117400611018_1885508556_n.jpg" alt="Poppin Cherry Chicken"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/poppin-cherry-chicken/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">97cd1e9f-9de5-45cf-8f45-b8159320ed46</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 01:51:02 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Summer Corn Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11421971_386701731520252_1465121388_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This type of salad seems to be a staple in my family for most summer BBQ’s. Since summer corn has such a small window, we make the most of it as long as we can. When we enjoy corn on the cob, we usually leave the husk on the corn and grill it just like that. For this, I thought I would switch it up and boil the corn then use my indoor grill since the weather was bad. This makes it an easy option if you are already in the kitchen cooking. However, if you are already grilling, throw those babies on the grill and you’ll have the same outcome. The salad is light and refreshing for the summer weather and pairs nicely with most meat and seafood dishes.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-h-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11420907_1459180354375471_1371722305_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint cherry tomatoes&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 ears corn&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;8 oz small mozzarella balls&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 scallions- sliced thin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1-2 tbsp honey&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;juice of 3-4 limes ~ 1/3 cup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by slicing the mozzarella balls in half. If the cherry tomatoes are large, you can slice these in half too. Slice the scallions and set all of these in a large bowl.  For the corn, you can grill it or boil it. I did both! A boil to cook it and a quick flip on the grill for color and some char. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11380172_952825744775770_1228231415_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I have a great trick for you to get the kernels off that cobb in the easiest and cleanest way possible.  See my picture below : place a small bowl upside down in a large bowl, then place the corn cobb on the base of the small bowl and stead it. Using a sharp knife, shave the kernels off from top to bottom, so that they fall nicely in the bowl. So easy!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11357682_334399986684030_1201146520_n.jpg" alt="Summer Corn Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the dressing, it is based on your preference. It is just lime juice with honey, and salt and pepper. You can add more honey for sweetness or more lime for more tartness. Also, if you are making this ahead, you may want to make extra dressing since it will soak into the veggies. This is such a delicious, colorful side dish for any barbeque, picnic, or dinner this summer!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/summer-corn-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">6f842036-42c9-4683-a19a-7350825b16ec</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 19 Jun 2015 19:35:13 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Blueberry Cheesecake Bars</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380738_935501613178740_1446684649_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This weekend we celebrated my Dad’s birthday. His one request was that we have a BBQ at his house and everyone makes something. My brother had a menu in mind, so we all split up the dishes evenly. My dad made the steak and lobster, my mom made the chimichurri sauce and sides, my brother made a summer grilled corn salad, Nate made fresh baked bread and trout dip, and I made an appetizer and this dessert! It was so much fun to have this delicious meal come together with everyones help. Everyone had one thing in mind: what does Dad like? That is exactly what inspired this dessert. I wanted to create something summery that my dad would love. Mission accomplished! Blueberry and lemon is a classic flavor combo that we all love. These bars were easy to make and were a great summer treat. They taste even better the next day.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Graham CrackerCrust &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup graham crackers - crushed&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ stick butter - melted&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp cinnamon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Cream Cheese Layer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 8oz packages of cream cheese - softened &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 eggs&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp vanilla&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Blueberry Pie Layer&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 pint fresh blueberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the zest of 1 lemon&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tsp cornstarch&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp sugar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Set oven to 325.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To make the crust : either use a food processor to grind the graham crackers or you can place in a large bag and crush them. Melt the butter and mix the 2 together. Press the mixture into an 8 x 8 square baking dish. I usually spray my dish with PAM non-stick cooking spray to be safe.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the cream cheese layer : using a food processor or hand mixer, blend the ingredients together. Once blended until smooth, spread evenly on top of graham cracker crust. Place in the oven on 325 degrees for about 30 minutes, until cooked through.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While the bars are baking, make the blueberry filling. In a small saucepan, put blueberries, sugar, and lemon zest in. Heat for about 5 minutes until simmering. Then, add cornstarch and let the mixture simmer for about 5 more minutes until it starts to thicken.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11380839_1162620157087675_1078370118_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once the pan comes out of the oven, let it cool slightly. Pour blueberry filling on top to cover the cream cheese layer. At this point, it is best to put in the fridge to chill. Once chilled, you can add more lemon zest on top. Cut the bars into squares and enjoy! We found that they were actually better the second day because everything had a chance to firm up. A great make-ahead summer dish!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11335163_627231654124948_996940625_n.jpg" alt="Blueberry Cheesecake Bars"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/blueberry-cheesecake-bars/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">20df2477-d14b-4daa-97a6-351b994a716d</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2015 01:38:16 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Shrimp Tacos with Mango Salsa</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-c-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11328330_1436884929951866_445870342_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It is Taco Tuesday at the Bowser’s and shrimp is on the menu tonight! We love tacos in all shapes, flavors, and forms and have eaten our fair share. I like to switch it up, and use seafood and shrimp in tacos, instead of always pork or beef.  The shrimp come out a little spicy and very flavorful, with an added zing from some lime zest. The mango salsa is sweet and also a little spicy from the jalapeno. I like to buy the mangoes when they are on sale and leave them on my counter for a few days to ripen. Then I get to decide what to make with them! The best is just to eat them super ripe and juicy. I like the added crunch of the slaw and the creamy consistency is a nice balance to the taco. Make these for your next taco night!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11327090_779461435508748_556561080_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Shrimp&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb peeled and deveined shrimp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp cumin&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp chili powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp garlic powder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ tsp paprika&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;lime zest from 1 lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ tsp salt&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;corn or flour tortillas&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salsa&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 mango - diced&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 jalapeno - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red onion - diced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tbsp cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ red pepper - chopped&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lime&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Slaw&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;¼ head cabbage - shredded&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp mayo&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;the juice of 1 lime &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful chopped cilantro&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the salsa: Mix ingredients and let the flavors mingle. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-g-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11272799_1452172171745662_1890611574_n.jpg" alt="Mango Slaw"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the Slaw: Mix the ingredients and let the flavors mingle. Set aside.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For the shrimp : Make sure shrimp are peeled and deveined. Lets be honest, I love it when they are available that way in the store, and even more when they are on sale, but that is not the norm. Set aside some time to prep the shrimp. Make sure shrimp are rinsed, drained, and pat them dry. Add the remaining ingredients from the list (cumin-salt) to the shrimp. At this point, you can let these marinate for a bit, or you can get ready to cook them up. They do not need long to marinate.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-lga1-1.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11282789_786614401445554_1845796248_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp Tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You have some options. You can pan fry the shrimp in 1-2 tsp of olive oil, which is what I did. You can also throw the shrimp on skewers and grill them, if the weather permits. I would prefer to grill the shrimp to get a nice char, but it has been raining all day. They are delicious either way!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To serve, add a few shrimp to each tortilla and top with slaw and salsa. Dig in!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11296754_1041953755832593_22856041_n.jpg" alt="Shrimp tacos"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/shrimp-tacos-with-mango-salsa/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">dcafd733-83ee-4866-894b-93a4ee700664</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 03 Jun 2015 01:45:46 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Flounder Puttanesca</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-e-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11325764_974861889221028_1373965387_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Flounder! I must say, this is a new fish for me. It all started 2 weeks ago when my family and I went on a birthday dinner for my mom and I. Our birthdays are a month apart, so we settled on a date in the middle. We chose an Italian restaurant and the first special of the night was Flounder Puttanesca. I thought to myself - “I will definitely not be having that, I am not even sure if I like flounder”. My brother decided to order that special and after tasting all of the meals, we unanimously voted his meal as the best meal of the night! There you have it, try new things and they may become new favorites.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Puttanesca sauce is not even something I have often, but it really is simple and delicious. It has a nice salty, briny flavor. I was able to recreate this dish pretty easily and I wanted to share it because it is easy enough for a weeknight meal, but also special enough for a dinner party. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;There is one ingredient I would like to address - the anchovies. I think some people may be opposed to trying this in the recipe, but I want to assure you that it will not give the sauce a “fishy” taste. What it will do, is give the sauce an added saltiness and really compliment the flounder. The anchovies basically melt into the sauce and there are not large pieces or bites. You will basically not even know they are in there. I would advise you to try them!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-d-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xfa1/t51.2885-15/11326400_1593491014265099_2049629446_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;4 flounder fillets, or approximately 1 pound&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup flour, for dusting&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;canola oil for frying&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 large can whole peeled tomatoes (28 oz)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 tbsp olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup pitted kalamata olives&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;anchovies packed in oil - 4-5 small fillets &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;3 oz capers, ~ 3 tbsp&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;6 garlic cloves, grated or minced fine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp red pepper flakes (optional)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 lb pasta - your choice, we used angel hair&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Remove flounder and dry the fillets. Add salt and pepper to both sides and then dip each fillet into the flour. You want a light dusting on the fish. Add canola oil to a heavy bottomed pan about an inch up the side. You want to do a shallow fry and not submerge the whole fish in oil. My fillets were pretty thin, so they only needed 3 minutes per side. When you remove them from the oil, put them on a paper-towel lined plate to soak any excess oil.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add olive oil to a skillet over medium low heat.  Add in the sardine fillets and let them cook in the oil. Using a wooden spoon, break them apart. They will melt into the oil and sauce and you will not have chunks in there after a few minutes.  Add in the garlic and let everything cook for a minute.  Add in capers and cook for another minute. Next, use your hands to crush the whole tomatoes as you add them into the pan. This way, you will have smaller, bite-sized chunks of tomatoes in the sauce. Let the sauce come to a simmer to incorporate all the flavors. After a few minutes, add in the red pepper flakes (if using) and the calamata olives. The sauce doesn’t need to cook much after this, but I would simmer it for a few minutes. &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-b-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11327119_885127478212681_946569875_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point, you can add the pasta into the sauce to mingle. Or, if you prefer, you can serve the pasta topped with sauce, then the fish on top of that and more sauce to finish. I added the pasta into the sauce then served it with a piece of fish on top and more sauce over the whole dish. It was really delicious, fresh, salty, and wonderful!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-f-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11247676_1631879270382925_89241324_n.jpg" alt="Flounder Puttanesca"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Manjia!&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/f/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">1bd99e70-9087-4bfd-88d4-33ea2694c6a4</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 28 May 2015 00:45:15 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title>Spinach Poppy Salad</title><description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://scontent-atl.cdninstagram.com/hphotos-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11243850_366276456900133_308885176_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I want to start by saying that I am sorry for posting another salad recipe this soon, but I absolutely have to share this one! Plus, it’s spring-time and I think we all can use a little more salad in our lives. This dressing is a real winner.  It is sweet, savory, and salty, with a nice bite from the onion.  The ingredients go nicely together and really compliment and balance each other. This salad makes a great lunch or side for dinner. I think it would also be lovely at a BBQ as a light and fresh option.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As always, of course you can tweak the salad ingredients to use what you have and what you like. That is what I always do, and that is what inspired this salad! Hope you enjoy.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Salad&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;spinach leaves&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 cup cooked whole wheat pasta (optional - I used leftovers)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;sliced strawberries&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup of crumbled feta - to taste&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;handful roasted sunflower seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Poppy Seed Dressing &lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;⅓ cup white vinegar&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;½ cup olive oil&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp white sugar &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;2 tbsp grated white onion &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 tsp poppy seeds&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;1 heaping tbsp dijon mustard &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Begin by making the dressing. Add the sugar to the vinegar and whisk until sugar is dissolved, about 2 minutes. Next, add grated onion - I use a regular box grater on the large holes to do this. This will give you the onion flavor without the sharp bite. Add the dijon mustard and then the olive oil and whisk until emulsified. Add the poppy seeds at the end.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Add the spinach and pasta to a large bowl and continue to add each layer on top. Mix with dressing and serve with extra sunflower seeds on top for a little added crunch!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://igcdn-photos-a-a.akamaihd.net/hphotos-ak-xaf1/t51.2885-15/11252886_691378404342000_1821008213_n.jpg" alt="Spinach Poppy Salad"&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description><link>http://barebonescooking.com/spinach-poppy-salad/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">0d1023ff-0228-4151-baf5-0c2f50e248d3</guid><dc:creator>Kristina Bowser</dc:creator><pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:32:30 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
